My mom isn't a normal mom.
I know that.
She operates differently.
Ginny, the rules weren't made
to help people like us.
So why follow 'em?
♪ She's got silver bullets on her tongue ♪
♪ He's deep under her spell ♪
♪ I'm screamin' out
But it just won't help ♪
♪ I think I'm cursed
I had him first ♪
♪ Adeline, have mercy
You don't wanna break my heart… ♪
We've never been the normal
picket fence, dinner at 7:00 family.
♪ Don't take my man… ♪
Everything she's done,
she's done for me.
I can get past this.
We can be okay.
♪ Put the gun down ♪
♪ Ooh-oh-oh, ooh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Ooh-oh-oh, ooh-oh-oh… ♪
- Hey.
- Shh. I don't want my mom to hear.
♪ Put the gun down ♪
I'm… I'm on my period.
But I can… I can…
I can just...
♪ Only and I can't lie… ♪
Sorry.
♪ That I'd rather stay at home ♪
♪ That you're reading between the lines ♪
♪ That's just my mood, right
Sunset turns to moonlight ♪
♪ Finally time to do right
Baby by you do right… ♪
Just a little gentler.
Sorry, I've never done
this before.
No, it's okay, it's just...
Um, just be careful.
♪ If we got hope, then we'll make it… ♪
Okay. Um, teeth.
Ginny.
- Shit. Get in the closet.
- Shit.
Okay, uh…
Marcus.
You're up.
It's only 9:00 p.m.
I forgot to pick up
our birth control from CVS.
- Be a peach and run out and grab it.
- You can't grab it tomorrow morning?
Oh, yeah, that's fun.
Let's play fast and loose
with our birth control.
Remind me of our age difference again?
It's one, two… fifteen years?
Come on, move your butt.
Marcus, are you in the closet?
Yeah.
Are you decent?
No.
Get dressed and come out here, please.
Hi there!
Hi.
- I'm gonna go.
- How long you been dating my daughter?
We're not, like, dating. It's, um…
Hmm.
I didn't like that answer.
- No, I really like her.
- You like her?
- I love her.
- You love her?
Yeah, I do.
Have a seat.
Mm.
You're a damaged kid, aren't you?
It's okay. I know.
I'm damaged too.
Ginny is special.
She's gonna go off
and do big, wonderful things.
And I realized something recently.
She doesn't know it yet, but one day,
when she figures out that our damage
is holding her back, she's gonna leave us.
And I'm not being cruel.
Well, maybe I'm being cruel,
but… I'm being honest.
You're her high school love,
and that is fine.
That's sweet, that's swell, pin her.
Take her to sock hop, or whatever.
But when the time comes,
if you really love her,
don't hold her back.
Hey.
Promise me.
Yeah, I promise.
And if you get her pregnant,
I'll kill you.
Mom, the pharmacy said
that you picked it up this morning.
What is this?
Oh, Marcus stopped by for a smoke
on his way out of your closet.
Mm, so this is the trust thing
we were talking about?
You tell me.
Were you gonna share
that your secret boyfriend
was sneaking through your window?
- He's not my boyfriend...
- Yeah, now's the time for semantics.
Sneaking a boy through a window.
Am I trapped in a '90s show?
What is this?
Clarissa Explains It All? Dawson's Creek?
What's next episode?
Someone have a mental breakdown
or hook up with a teacher?
I'm definitely tuning in.
I'm gonna get out of here, uh…
Yeah, this is, uh…
this is really fit mothering.
Food stamps are 210 a month.
I only make 250.
Rent is 500.
That brings us back to the conversation
about my electric bill,
and I promise you,
not even Benjamin Franklin
wanted to talk this much
about electricity.
I've been transferred three times.
Okay? I'm tired.
Please don't transfer.
You can't turn it off
if my kid is sick, right?
It's a law.
You hear that?
Another month.
Thank you.
How about this?
I won't be mad you've been sneaking
a boy through the window
if you're not mad
that I smoked with that boy.
Come on, I want us to be okay.
- What did you guys talk about?
- Patriots are nothing without Brady.
Mom.
I wanted to know how he felt about you.
And?
He's in love with you.
He's got good taste,
I'll give him that.
- I just wish you'd told me about him.
- Well, I'm sorry I'm not perfect.
Yeah, well, neither am I.
Yeah, no kidding.
Hey.
What?
Um…
Do you remember...
What's the thing with the…
with the balls?
With the what?
One time, you said that
there was a trick with, um…
…with balls.
Are you asking me how to give a blow job?
Yeah.
After you just yelled at me
for not being a fit mother?
Okay.
So you wanna apply pressure
to the bottom with one hand.
- Uh, what do I do with my other hand?
- Just kind of…
Maybe we need a banana.
- Wait. I know. Let me get my vibrator.
- Don't get your vibrator.
So it's Marcus, huh?
Mr. Weed smoking, breaking and entering,
"first time I touch my bike,
I crash into a tree" Marcus?
- That's the guy?
- He's much more than that.
Mm-hmm. Clearly.
He also likes getting head.
He's actually a really talented artist.
Mm-hmm. True Renaissance man.
He take you on dates,
or he just sneaks in at night?
Mom, stop, okay? Just trust me.
- Okay.
- Tomorrow's his birthday.
Very nice.
Very literal.
Good, good.
Whoo! Weird night.
No more secrets, Peach.
That's the only way this works, okay?
Yeah.
This is good.
We're good now.
The air's all been cleared, right,
with everything?
Yes. Yeah, we're good. I'm good.
If anything,
we're closer than ever.
Us against the world.
Yeah, Mom, I know.
Okay.
Good.
Okay, coffee maker in the house.
Is that the last of it?
Uh, well, you would think that,
but you would be wrong.
I do not know how I have that much crap.
Hey, Ginny.
You think you and Austin
can stay at Zion's this Friday?
Paul and I are gonna crash at his condo
after we finish cleaning it out.
- This Friday? Yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
My freedom. It's the end of an era.
So, family, I have to throw a party for
my initiation to the Neighborhood Club.
What do we think? What's my theme?
- Has to have a theme?
- What household were you raised?
There's opportunity for theme,
you take it.
What's the theme of your wedding?
Oh, well, I stand corrected,
wedding themes are tacky.
- The theme of our wedding is wedding.
- And love.
Yeah.
I wanna throw the best party
in the history of parties.
Babe, it's going to be great.
Yeah, babe.
You're all a bunch of assholes.
Is that what you're wearing?
Couldn't let me leave the house
without making one comment, could you?
No, I like it.
It's very "I'm the new vampire
who just drove into Sunnydale."
Edgy.
Okay. Yeah, no, Paul, if you ever
need to unwind from all of this,
just hit me up.
Maybe you and I can go smoke out.
If this is a cry for help, it's very loud.
Does she seem okay to you?
Yeah. I mean, she seems fine.
You two seem back to normal.
- I mean, normal for the two of you.
- Hmm.
But what was up
with the "smoke out" comment?
She's teasing me.
We had a little incident last night.
I caught Marcus Baker
climbing through her window.
- Her window? In this house?
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay, so, what are we gonna do?
Send her to boarding school
in Switzerland?
- No, Georgia, I'm serious.
- No, I know, me too.
I don't know. I'll take care of it.
Okay, you take care of it.
Mom, we're gonna be late.
Okay.
- Bye, buddy.
- Let's go.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
Hey, real quick. How did the meeting
with Austin's teacher go?
Oh, she wants to put him
on some kind of plan.
I have to meet
with the guidance counselor.
I don't know.
Doesn't matter, I'm not doing it.
Why not? If she recommends it, then it's...
Well, he just needs to study harder.
- Maybe, but...
- Well, I'll take care of it. Don't worry.
I'll see you at work. I love you.
Happy my birthday to you guys.
♪ And happy my birthday ♪
…to you, both of you.
Yes, happy my birthday!
♪ What's the hardest part ♪
Happy my birthday to you guys.
Yes, it's my birthday.
♪ And it's my birthday ♪
♪ I'm turning 16, and I'm so excited ♪
Oh! You didn't have to do this!
Weird. I didn't.
♪ An event I witnessed ♪
♪ What's the hardest part ♪
♪ Of being alone? ♪
♪ I stood up, I went numb
I ran towards the exit ♪
♪ Left my head, left my friends… ♪
Hey, Max.
I just wanted to say
happy birthday.
Thanks, Sophie. That's really nice.
How are you? How are things?
Oh, I'm… I' good. Yeah. How are you?
Great. Having the best birthday.
You should come to my party on Friday.
It's at Brodie's basement.
As friends, obviously.
And you could bring someone,
like a friend or a date.
It wouldn't matter to me.
Uh, yeah, maybe.
Uh, happy birthday.
♪ End of me Washed up teen… ♪
What do you think she meant
when she said "maybe"?
♪ It' s the shake of a fist
Feel the guilt… ♪
You can't be mad at me on my birthday.
- What was that last night?
- She just knew I was there.
She's Georgia, she knows everything.
She has no boundaries.
Expect that shit from her.
Welcome to my life.
I'm sorry.
- What'd you guys talk about?
- Nothing.
Just what my intentions are
with her daughter.
And what did you say?
I said I intend to destroy you.
Don't smoke with my mom again.
I can't believe
I have to say that sentence.
Happy birthday.
You tend to confuse
the days of the week, so…
Okay.
Glad you like it.
I love it. Thanks.
There's more.
Um, my mom and Paul
are gonna be at Paul's this Friday,
so my house will be empty.
Yo, Maxine's a bitch.
- "Birthday."
- Thank you.
What you doing right now?
What class you have?
Um, I have AP English.
- Wanna skip? Hmm?
- Haven't you been skipping a lot?
Why don't you go smoke with my mom
and tell on me?
Hey, come in.
City's website is live.
"I will continue to be a tireless advocate
for Wellsbury residents."
You didn't run this by me?
- No, I didn't.
- You like it?
It's very dry.
Where's the mention that you're engaged?
- It's not People magazine.
- The picture is of City Hall.
That is where we work.
- It should be of you, you're hot.
- Nobody cares about that.
- Yes, they do.
I can help fix this.
We need a social media presence
to humanize you.
- An account run by the mayoress.
- Still not a thing.
Nick, you know I'm right.
Paul's charismatic. He's good-looking.
Okay, starting to feel like
a piece of meat.
He's got Beto energy. Obama energy.
Oh, oh yes, he's exactly like Obama,
a Black man who worked his way
to the highest office in the world.
The very same.
Socials aren't a bad idea.
We could hire someone.
Why won't you let me help?
I could ask you the same thing.
What Steinbeck is doing here
is making a clear connection
between the importance of redemption
in order to survive spirituality.
You see, the family manages to survive
and perform an act of kindness,
showing that they have not lost
their sense of decency.
So if you put that into context…
Got up at 6:00 a.m.
I raided Party City,
and I even used glitter glue.
She's being such a mean girl.
She'll get over it.
She's mad that we weren't
being good friends,
but she's not being good to us.
I feel like she would freak out
if she knew that we were all hanging out.
- Wanna take a picture?
- I think I do.
Let's do it.
- Get in this.
- No, uh…
This dance is pivotal, okay?
We just met Josephine.
Independent.
Marriage? Absolutely not.
And we met the duke,
you know, lone wolf, anti-establishment.
And then they meet each other.
And then, oh, Josephine realizes
she has feelings for the duke.
The duke realizes
he has feelings for Josephine.
They pretend… they don't.
And it goes…
Carriage up, and turning, box, two, three.
Promenade, twinkle step, and close.
Here.
Okay.
Carriage up.
Sorry.
Uh, he lost me at "promenade."
- Uh, Max, you wanna come here?
- Yeah.
- Do you mind putting your arm down?
- Yes. Sorry.
It's my birthday.
I'm very popular and beloved.
Ooh, happy birthday.
Thank you.
Happy my birthday to you.
Actually, you should totally come
to my party on Friday.
It's at Brodie's basement.
Whole cast and crew's invited.
Yeah? Uh, maybe.
Hey, will my costume have cleavage?
You'll like it, I promise.
I have this whole steampunk
meets Victorian high society concept
for the whole show.
- Okay, that sounds amazing.
- Doesn't it sound so good?
Yes. I'm so impressed.
Actually, I've always
really noticed your style.
- Really?
- Yeah. Oh, I love your whole look.
Thanks.
You too. I love your shirt.
Um, turn around.
- Hey.
Sorry I'm late. Did Joe notice?
- He's not here.
- Okay.
Hey, Marcus.
Hey.
What? We steal coffee, like, all the time.
See ya.
How's that going?
Um, it's… it's good.
Is he your boyfriend?
- Um…
- Yeah, sounds about right.
Hey, what, uh… what sociopath orders
a gingerbread latte?
- That sounds vile. Mmm.
- It is. I had it this morning. Gross.
Oh my God. Joe.
What happened to your face?
What?
Okay, yeah, uh, first rule of Fight Club
is you do not talk about Fight Club.
Cute.
Second rule of Fight Club is
you do not talk about Fight Club.
- Am I paying you both for this?
- It's free.
- This is a new look.
- You like it?
It's very Hot Topic.
What?
- What the heck is Hot Topic?
- I don't know, but I think he insulted me.
Cynthia, would you like a refill?
- It's 4:00 p.m. somewhere, right?
- It's 4:00 p.m. here. 4:15, actually.
Oh, that's good.
If you're about to ask me
how I'm doing, don't.
I'm not doing well,
and I don't wanna talk about it...
Oh my God, what happened to your eye?
Well, if you're not talking,
I'm not either.
Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe.
I need help only you can provide.
- Goody.
- I need your caterer menu.
I'm throwing a party
at the Neighborhood Club.
You're looking at their newest member.
- Congratulations.
- Who punched you in the face?
What party did you throw
when you were a new member?
- Tom and I did a tailgating party.
- Oh.
We hired some high school football players
to wear their uniforms and pass out wings,
- and Tom tapped a keg.
- Mm.
Sounds really fun. Damn it.
Hey, Peach,
can you make me a gingerbread latte?
You're invited too, Joe.
You don't have to invite me
if you just want me to cater.
I'm inviting you
because I want you to come.
We're friends.
And I want you to cater.
Thank you.
Hello, Ellen.
I come waving a white flag.
- Well, white wine. Same thing.
- What do you want, Georgia?
I'm in the middle of making
the twins' birthday dinners, okay?
And Marcus wants burgers,
and Maxine wants chicken ziti, so…
I messed up. I should have told you
about Marcus and Ginny.
I don't have a good excuse.
I should have, and I'm sorry.
I usually handle everything myself, and…
I don't know how to explain it
other than that, but…
…I miss you.
I miss my friend.
Okay. I miss you too.
Here. You might wanna pour that.
I learned my lesson,
and I came over to tell you
that Marcus is climbing through
Ginny's window again.
I caught him last night.
Who does he think he is?
Christian Slater in Heathers?
Oh, that's a good one.
I didn't think of that one.
Unbelievable. Do they think we're stupid?
Yeah.
Why can't they just date
and use the front door?
Oh no, you are not snacking
after I made
two separate birthday dinners.
Mommy, there are no rules on birthdays.
Hi, Georgia.
Happy birthday, Max.
- Got fun birthday plans?
- None that Ginny's invited to.
Maxine, it is not nice to hold a grudge.
People make mistakes.
And if you push everyone away,
you will not have anyone left.
Marcus, I'm gonna kill you!
♪ Think that I'll break?
Well, I can handle that… ♪
Seriously? Ginny wasn't enough for you,
you had to take Abby too?
Why are you doing this to me
on my birthday?
Our birthday.
And I didn't do anything to you.
♪ And just F me up, yeah, mess me up… ♪
You don't get to be the decider
of the moral high ground.
♪ But I've got soap to clean this heart ♪
♪ So, who are you to say
You don't want to mess me up ♪
♪ Mess me up ♪
- Hey.
All right.
- Oh no, not that dr...
- Wow.
- Okay.
- What do we have here?
- Yeah, ha-ha.
- There's so many of them.
- Okay.
- They're like jelly beans or...
- I found their leader.
- Okay.
- Big Daddy.
- All right. Put it back now.
- How's this one even work?
- Come on. All right.
- Oh, Big Daddy.
- Paul. Paul, stop.
- Oh, he's got a mind of his own.
- Put it back.
- Be gentle, Big Daddy.
- Very good.
Be gentle, Big Daddy.
Where does this even go?
Hey, Mom, I can't find my…
I need to knock. I know that now.
I'm just really gunning for
that Mother of the Year award, huh?
What do you think?
Should I be worried
I screwed her up so bad
she's about to freebase heroin
and join the circus?
What?
Nothing. I just... I...
You know what? Can I ask you something
without you getting mad?
Mm. No promises.
Austin.
Could you help me understand
why you wouldn't do
what his teacher recommend...
I'm mad.
I'm serious.
Look, I… I watched my parents
go through very similar things with Chris.
- Austin and Chris aren't the same.
- I know they're not.
I'm not saying they are.
But, you know, Austin might also benefit
from a little bit of extra attention,
and there are resources available.
I'm not slapping a label on him
that'll follow him around his whole life.
That changes how the world sees him.
He's fine,
and I don't wanna talk about this.
Why deny him the help?
You don't have to do this yourself.
They're not your kids!
Wow.
- Um…
- Hey, that came out too harsh.
I just mean that I've got it.
Okay? That's all.
- Okay? I...
- No. You know what?
No. I… I hear you loud and clear.
Okay? Boundary is very well set.
I will not be told
about Ginny's new boyfriend.
I will not be trusted
to try and help with Austin.
Oh, like how you trust me at work?
What is that supposed to mean?
Well, I've proven myself again and again,
and I'm still not being looped in.
It's like we got engaged
and I'm getting cut out. What is that?
Okay, is this about Nick? Because
I understand that he's been a little...
No, I know how Nick's been.
I don't care. You're the boss.
And you put Big Daddy
back where you found him.
Hey.
Sorry about that.
Good for you.
Good for Paul, really. Surprising.
Hey, Peach, there is something
I wanted to talk to you about.
- God.
- No, nothing bad.
Um…
I'm getting married,
and you're my best friend.
Will you be my maid of honor?
Mom, yes, of course.
- Yeah?
- Yes.
Aw!
I just don't wanna
have messed you up too bad.
Have I messed you up?
No, I'm okay.
Okay.
All right.
- Yay!
This is a great little shortcut
if you're not doing a full eyeliner
across the actual skin on your lid,
but it still gives you that sort of depth
and darkness, um, in that area.
To define the lid a little better,
I'm gonna put more of that pencil
near the outer corner of the eye.
♪ Yeah, he know he's just a number
And he good with that ♪
♪ Play along 'cause he know
I got a super WAP ♪
♪ Issa bad affair and he knew that ♪
♪ If you can't hit it
Right where your crew at? ♪
♪ I need a…
With a tongue like a motor ♪
♪ Stroke game that gon' put me in a coma ♪
♪ He got a…
But I don't owe her ♪
♪ Treat him like my son
Put that in a stroller ♪
♪ Imma take it like a bandit, yeah ♪
♪ Keep it up
Can you manage? Yeah ♪
♪ Throw it back, give it back back, yeah ♪
♪ Tag me in, I'ma tag back, yeah ♪
♪ Going twelve rounds
Hittin' back to back ♪
♪ Only twelve rounds
Can you handle that? ♪
♪ Need a big dog for my tiny cat ♪
♪ From the windows to the walls
To the welcome mat ♪
♪ Woo! ♪
♪ Pump the breaks like, woo ♪
♪ Take a breath like, woo ♪
♪ Been a minute like, woo ♪
I heard if you eat a tarantula,
it's supposed to taste like earthy crack.
I knew you were gonna say
something like that.
Like, just the crunchiness…
I like your hair.
Thanks.
Yeah, I've always wanted to dye my hair.
Do you remember when we were 11
and we stole beer from your dad
and poured it on our heads
to lie out in the sun
to try and get highlights?
We were so embarrassing.
- We should've just drank the beer.
- We should've just... So true.
♪ Having fun now, come on ♪
♪ Oh, it's happening now ♪
Max.
♪ I can feel it deep inside of me… ♪
- Okay, she's being so dramatic.
- She's being absurd.
It's kind of funny.
- Things have been a lot better.
- Let's talk more about your mother.
Can we not refer to her as my "mother"?
It's very Kathy Bates.
What's your relationship like?
Well, uh, she's not really like
a normal mom.
She was just smoking weed
with my boyfriend.
I guess he's not officially my boyfriend.
How do you feel about her doing that?
She just does stuff like that.
Is this stressful for you?
No. I mean, that's just what she's like.
Can I ask you a question?
Of course.
How much of who you are
and what you're capable of
is predetermined?
Like… Like, by genetics or whatever?
Why are you asking me that?
It was just a dumb thought. It's nothing.
This is the moment
you identify what you're feeling
and what makes you want to self-harm.
You have to be honest
about how you're really feeling,
or it won't get better.
Yeah.
Yeah, I know.
Like I said, I'm... I'm fine.
I like the blue. It's a nice touch.
Thanks.
So your mom asked me
to take you and Austin for Friday night.
Oh, um, actually just Austin.
I'll be spending the night
at a friend's house.
Mm.
Simone?
It's no one. Um, how's school?
Max hates me.
You'd be surprised how little
people actually think about you.
Okay, normally I'd agree with you,
but I can assure you Max hates me,
and she thinks about it a lot.
Have you tried speaking to her?
Okay, you don't like that idea. Um…
How's Bracia?
The guy she likes
commented "fire" on the picture you took,
so you basically made her entire life.
And how's therapy?
I'm not burning
if that's what you're asking.
That's not what I asked.
Therapy's working.
I'm much better.
So tell me about this "no one" Simone.
Anthony Green…
Do you…
…remember any details?
Do I remember a missing person's case
from over a decade ago?
It's New Orleans. Do you know
how many of these we deal with?
Yeah.
- What?
- His wife.
I do remember her. I felt bad for her.
Pretty young gal.
Looks like your memory's been jogged.
He ran an illegal gambling ring,
which she took the fall for.
She got booked,
and as soon as she got out, he bolted.
Shameful.
So she was never a person of interest
in his disappearance?
How's she gonna take a man down
and move a body? Look at her.
Uh, must be very convenient for her.
What?
Everyone underestimates her.
Hey.
- Hey, how was your dad's?
- It was good.
- Oh no.
- What?
Living room dance party!
♪ Yeah, I rock Gucci gang… ♪
I'm so tired of everyone
being so damn serious around here.
What is happening?
♪ Yeah, I know my drink
Might be all pretty pink… ♪
Paul, you need to know
what you're marrying into.
Okay, I can get down with this.
♪ You'd never know it ♪
♪ It ain't showing
In this downtown dress ♪
♪ But let's just say that the shade
Of this lipstick matches my neck ♪
♪ 'Cause I can drive your truck
Faster than you can ♪
♪ I can get it done
With my own two hands ♪
♪ I can dance with the ladies ♪
♪ Drink with the fellers ♪
♪ You know Fridays are good
But boy with me they'd be better ♪
♪ Country boys sure know how to have fun ♪
♪ But let me show you
How a country girl gets it done, y'all ♪
♪ Keep up ♪
♪ Oh, yeah, keep up ♪
♪ I bet you can't keep up… ♪
Um, I'm gonna head out.
Oh, uh, wait, when's your curfew?
My curfew?
- Yeah. She got a curfew, right?
- Yeah.
- I do?
- I don't know.
♪ Can't have you falling behind… ♪
I'll be back at a reasonable hour.
Hey, Peach, you okay?
Yeah, I'm good.
Let's go.
Whoo!
♪ I can get it done
With my own two hands… ♪
Come on now.
♪ I can dance with the ladies ♪
♪ Drink with the fellers ♪
♪ You know Friday are good
But boy with me they'd be better ♪
♪ Country boys sure know how to have fun ♪
♪ But let me show you
How a country girl gets it done, y'all ♪
♪ Keep up ♪
Ginny! Didn't see you
come through the front door.
This is cozy.
Just gonna slide in here.
Okay, what are we talking about?
My mom told you, didn't she?
Let's just hang out here all night.
Looks like they made up, huh?
Okay, I don't get it.
I'm not the one who did anything wrong.
Yeah, babe, I don't know.
I got bad news, mi amors.
My basement flooded.
- Okay, that better be a euphemism.
- Sorry, no party tonight.
Okay, this cannot be happening to me.
Well, look on the bright side.
Now it doesn't matter
that you lost all your friends.
Oof.
- I'm kidding.
- Love you, Max.
- Hey, Ginny.
- Bye, Ginny.
- No, no! Excuse me. No.
- What do you want now?
I'm the one who's mad, not you.
Oh, I'm sorry, Max. Did I disrupt
the equilibrium of the universe
by suggesting that something
not be centered around you?
Okay, ouch. And also, bitch.
You're the one in the wrong here.
Oh, you love that, don't you?
You love that I screwed up
and you're perfect.
I'm not perfect,
but I didn't sleep with your brother.
- Good, because that'd be a felony.
- You lied to me, Ginny!
So freaking what?
I'm supposed to tell you everything?
That's not what friendship is.
Friendship is not having to reveal
every innermost thought and secret
to each other.
To me, friendship is
about supporting each other.
It seems to me that a friend
wouldn't write off someone
without having the full story.
The full story?
Do I need a play-by-play
of how you boned my brother?
'Cause I'm pretty sure
I know how that went.
"Oh, Ginny, I'm dark
and gloomy and colors hurt my eyes."
"Oh, Marcus,
I'm finding myself."
"Will you point the way with your penis?"
You talk a lot, but it's not all quality.
Ooh, look who dyed her hair
and grew a backbone.
Are you gonna apologize or what?
- That's a joke.
- It's not, Max.
Because I love you.
Okay? I love you so much,
and you've hurt me.
God. Sometimes I just...
I feel like what I'm going through
and who I am
is just completely invisible to you.
I tried to not love your brother,
I really did.
But, I don't know, you Bakers have some
pheromone-y DNA or something.
- You love him?
- Yes.
Like real, real love? Like his greasy hair
doesn't bug you at all?
Yes.
I didn't know that.
I get him, and he gets me.
And we really tried to stop it,
because I love you too.
So you'd be like my sister-in-law.
Okay, well, that's…
that's aggressive, but…
I'm really sorry I've been so mean.
I've just been hurting so much,
it's leaking out of me like a faucet.
And I've been such a bitch,
a huge bitchity bitch.
And it's probably good
that Brodie's basement flooded
because I don't really have friends
to bring to my party.
I just want us to be okay.
Me too.
I really miss you.
What's this, the band's back together?
No.
No, Ginny, no.
- Yes. Yes, Ginny, yes.
- You don't know what we're talking about.
I don't, but I know I want it to happen.
Fine.
For your birthday,
you can have my birthday.
Yay!
What does that mean?
- Party at my house.
- What?
Okay.
I'm violently excited. Let's do it.
Thanks.
Mm-hmm.
- Georgia. Paul.
- Joe!
We're celebrating
Paul's last night of freedom.
He's officially moved in tomorrow.
End of an era.
Oh, of course. Congrats.
Um, let me get you
a bottle of wine on the house.
Oh, you don't have to...
Hmm.
I think Joe might have
a little crush on you.
Oh, stop. No, he doesn't.
Okay.
Hmm.
Yes!
Okay!
- You shouldn't be talking about me.
- Oh, all right…
He is so... Listen, you guys...
- Cheers.
- Yay.
Yay!
Mistakes were made… by me.
Feelings were hurt,
and I wish I could change things.
Regrets abound.
Is this an apology?
I'm sorry.
I'm a dick, and I love you.
Let's do coffee shop.
Bing, bing, bing...
- Caramel macchiato on the house.
- Here's your change.
I'm making a leaf 'cause I'm an artiste.
Here you go, it's hot.
So much!
You guys are weird.
My little love-stricken cherub,
angel, princess, demon.
- Marcus, huh? You have terrible taste.
- Thank you.
Yo, this has little gold flecks in it
that actually rip holes in your throat
so the alcohol enters
your bloodstream faster.
Perfect!
- You want?
- Yes.
To MANG!
Oh, you weren't… you weren't lying.
- Hi.
- Hey.
- That's discussing.
Come upstairs.
I'll get some drinks.
I'm contact pregnant.
You're so cute.
Rehearsal was fun.
Yeah, I'm… I'm just so awkward though.
We just need a little more practice.
- Here?
- Mm-hmm.
In the kitchen?
- Oh my god, Silver! Yay!
- Oh!
Oh my God, yay. I'm so glad you're here.
Are you having fun?
- So much fun.
- That's good. I'm so glad.
Why isn't Sophie here yet?
Do you think she's not coming?
I asked her to come.
- Do you want another shot?
- Yeah.
Hey.
Um, can we talk?
- Like a really… a really good one, right?
- Mm.
- Hold on. Hey, Zion, what's up?
- Sorry to bother you.
I tried Ginny but she's not answering.
Is it okay for Austin
to watch a PG-13 movie?
You tried Ginny? Why would you...
PG-13 is fine. Gotta go.
Everything okay?
Mm-mm.
- Ellen? Hi. The little shits got us.
- Oh, hello.
So…
♪ I've been taken too long
With simple decisions ♪
You know, everyone blames me
for our breakup,
but it wasn't just me.
I know.
I'm sorry for saying
all that messed up shit to you.
I'm sorry too.
But what sucked the most
was that you didn't believe me,
about what happened.
You said I was being dramatic,
like I was the problem.
I know.
♪ I’m stuck peering over the edge ♪
♪ I was meant for the other side… ♪
Do you ever feel all this pressure
to just fit in everywhere
and act perfect all the time?
Yes. Constantly.
I shouldn't have punched Marcus.
I shouldn't have sent him that photo.
Yeah, that one stung.
♪ For the other side… ♪
I really loved you.
It's the first time I ever loved anyone.
Don't tell Samantha.
Please let me tell Samantha.
♪ 'Cause when I’m weak, I'm lost
I give in to questions … ♪
I loved you too, for what it's worth.
But not the same, right?
♪ Tell me when can I trust
My sense of direction? ♪
♪ Wake up and I’m on the wrong track ♪
♪ I was meant for the other side… ♪
Hey.
♪ I’m stuck peering over the edge… ♪
Make sure he's good to you.
You deserve it.
♪ I was meant for the other side ♪
♪ I’m stuck peering over the edge ♪
Don't tell anyone.
Seriously, what happened?
This?
Hockey game.
- Hockey game?
- Mm-hmm.
You play hockey?
- Yep. Right wing, Brookline Bulldogs.
- Huh.
- Lets me get out some energy.
- Energy?
Well, rage.
I love hockey.
Get out.
This year is gonna be the Leaf's year.
Out. Get out of my restaurant.
All right, fine.
We need a nickname.
Like… Garcus?
No, like something you call me.
Like honey pie?
Ew. No. No, something cute like, um…
Like Pooh Bear.
So for short you're just Poo.
- No, not Poo.
- No, I like it. It's cute.
- Little Poo? Little Turd Face?
- Why you're like this?
- Okay, no.
- Little Poo. No.
No, not Poo. Something else.
- Uh…
- Um…
What about "baby"?
Why are you doing this?
Doing what?
I'm not going anywhere.
I feel like you think I'm going somewhere,
like you don't trust…
I don't trust it.
If I learned anything from my mom,
it's don't trust anyone,
even her, especially her.
And all men. Never trust a man. So…
Well, I'm not going anywhere.
Neither am I.
Okay, Poo.
So then…
…what are we?
What do you mean?
I just wanna know your intentions.
What? Why can't you say it?
I don't know, I'm just…
I thought... I think I'm, uh…
I'm damaged, and I'm scared
I'm gonna screw this up.
I don't wanna screw this up.
I want you to be my girlfriend.
Don't look at me like that. Stop. Stop.
- I don't really do girlfriends, sorry.
- Yeah, yeah, okay.
I love you, Virginia Miller.
Today, tomorrow,
forever.
♪ Please dream of mine ♪
- No, you… you don't have to.
- It's okay.
Okay.
Oh shit.
Yeah, that's exactly what I'm saying.
♪ Moved to the 'burbs
And I still get ratchet ♪
♪ Ratchet, ratchet, ratchet, ratchet ♪
♪ Moved to the 'burbs
And I still get ratchet ♪
♪ Green like salad, ass cheeks tatted ♪
♪ Moved to the 'burbs
But I still get ratchet ♪
♪ Birkin bag baby going Birkin bag crazy ♪
♪ X on the box
But a busta couldn’t play me ♪
♪ Got ya man hooked
Like it's crack in the '80s ♪
♪ Hustle like a dude
But I ride it like a lady ♪
♪ Been on top
Now I can do what I want… ♪
A mother! It's a mother! A mother!
Coming out!
Yeah, my pleasure.
After you.
Oh God.
Have fun.
Welcome to our home.
Bye!
Guys!
Yay! How about a round
of applause for the real heroes, right?
For conceiving me.
Yay!
Mm.
- Come on.
- You guys want a drink?
No?
So why'd you look so spiffy tonight?
Had a date later.
Oh, that's fun.
Mmm. Not fun?
It just gets, uh, depressing
after a while.
Sorry, you're unlucky in love?
Why is that so hard to believe?
Because I have eyes.
Because hello.
And you have your own business.
No way.
There's got to be more to it.
Well, the person I wanna be with
just doesn't see me like that, so…
I'm sorry.
That's lonely.
Almost as lonely
as the person you wanna be with
not recognizing you anymore.
Tom didn't know my name today.
That's why I don't wanna go home.
Cheers.
If anything, anything would have happened,
your mother and I would've been liable.
Do you understand?
Yeah. I know, I'm sorry. It was dumb.
We expect more from you, Ginny.
- Georgia, do you have anything to add?
- Yeah.
Bad Ginny.
Okay.
Boy.
Hey, I'm sorry about the other night.
I love that you care about 'em.
I've just been the only one
looking after 'em for so long, I...
Listen, you are going to be a Randolph,
and they are going to be my kids too.
And I want that more than anything.
Okay.
Why are you so happy?
She threw a rager.
Like a Can't Hardly Wait,
American Pie rager.
Okay, and we're… happy about that?
Well, I didn't screw her up too bad.
She's a normal teenager. This is amazing.
Okay, if you say so.
Yeah.
I want so badly to be normal.
But I look around
and I feel like there's a wall
separating me from everybody else.
I understand why my mom did it.
She felt she had to.
She did it for me.
There's blood on my hands.
Me and her against the world.
Guilty.
♪ I aim to lose
I like to break the rules ♪
I like to break the rules… ♪
♪ I aim to lose
I like to break the rules ♪
I like to break the rules… ♪
Ginny?
Hi, Dr. Lily.
♪ I aim to lose… ♪
I... I'm...
I'm doing good.
Um, I… I am getting better.
Ginny, why'd you call?
Do you feel like you wanna self-harm?
♪ Everything's taboo
When it's been broken into two ♪
When it's been broken into two… ♪
I'm not okay.