Thanks for letting me put
Halley in your room.
Oh, no problem.
And Penny, she kinda threw up
on your stuffed bear.
Oh, that's okay.
Hey, (STUTTERS)
that's an Ewok and it's mine.
Yeah, which is why it's okay.
See, he gets Ewoks in his bed.
You've got Chewbacca, that's enough.
I used to have the stuffed raccoon
from Guardians of the Galaxy
but Cinnamon licked it raw.
There's a time and place
for your randy dog stories
and it's never and nowhere.
Yeah, no more stories about sex,
so Amy, that brings us to you.
Well, at work we've been doing
some interesting research
with neuroprosthetics.
Neat. I've been re-watching The O.C.,
so we're all leading productive lives.
We've been working
on a computer interface
that can use brain wave patterns
to control robotic limbs,
but we're having a little trouble
localizing the signal from the EEG cap.
Oh, well, have you thought about adding
a phased array of sensors
for better localization?
Actually, that never occurred to me.
It never occurred to me
I would miss the Ewok conversation.
Good, 'cause ljust bought
another one on Amazon.
You know, I could use
an engineer on this project.
Well, now, this works out great.
Howard's an engineer.
-(HOWARD CHUCKLES)
-l'm sure he knows someone qualified.
She's talking about me, Sheldon.
I'm perfectly qualified.
Yeah, Howie's the world's best engineer.
It says so right on his coffee mug.
- Aw, you got him a mug?
- I did.
But it's not a competition.
Yeah, I lost that battle years ago.
So, Howard, are you interested?
Are you kidding? If I could control
robot arms with my brain
I'd be able to do so many things.
Really? Because you've been controlling
human arms with your brain for years
and not much has come of it.
(THEME SONG PLAYING)
Hey, what you reading?
A parenting book.
Oh, my God. (STUTTERS) Are we...
What? No.
You think this is how I would tell you?
Well, (STAMMERS) you're sitting there
with a book.
It felt like anything was possible.
I don't know.
Bernadette left it here.
Oh, yeah? Anything interesting?
Well, I just saw a picture
of a baby's head crowning,
so I hope you enjoyed sex,
because we're done with that.
Hello.
- Hey, Sheldon, what's up?
- Hi.
Remember how disappointed you were
when Amy started driving me to work?
Sure the--
Sometimes people smile
a big smile of disappointment.
Yeah, well, good news,
Amy had to go in early
to show Howard around her lab,
so you get to drive me.
Aw, his smile of disappointment
has turned into a frown of joy.
It's fine.
I've been driving him for years,
what's one more day?
Oh, and I got
a new car game we can play.
It's called, "What siren am I?"
Kill me.
Amy, your lab is amazing.
A C-arm fluoroscope.
A cranial ultrasound.
(GASPS)
And look at that coffee maker.
I know. On our expense report,
I listed it as
"Eduardo," my Colombian lab assistant.
-(TSKS) So, this is it?
- Yes.
We're using it to map brainwave patterns
and then converting them
into electrical impulses
that can be used to control anything
from wheelchairs to robots.
Based on that ring on your finger,
I'd say you're pretty good
at controlling robots. (CHUCKLES)
Careful, that's my fiancé
you're talking about
and I can program him to hurt you.
(IMITATES SIREN SOUNDS)
I don't know, (STUTTERS) French police?
Oh, so close. Belgian ambulance.
All right. You ready for your next one?
And just a warning,
this one's a little annoying.
(IMITATES SIREN SOUNDS)
All right, all right. Let's take
a little break. I'm getting a headache.
Oh.
Right in the middle of our fun game.
Yeah, weird.
So, Howard and Amy working together,
that's interesting, huh?
Eh, it's all right, I suppose.
When usually when Amy complains
about her co-workers
I just tune her out,
but now I'll be able to join in
and pound away.
You're not jealous of Howard, are you?
You-- Of course not.
The only engineer I'm jealous of
is the one who blows the train whistle.
Ooh, that just gave me an idea
for a new game,
"What whistle am I?"
Train.
For your information,
it was going to be tea kettle,
but the tea kettle was on a train,
so I'll give it to you.
If we add phase detection
to your EEG sensors,
I'll have to rewrite most of the code.
Can you do that?
These hands were made
to do three things.
Close-up magic, writing code
and the dirty shadow puppet show
that got me kicked out of Hebrew school.
Hello.
Hi. What a nice surprise.
Well, ljust came by to see
how you two were getting along.
(CHUCKLES)
Well, everything's going really great.
Aw, that's nice to hear.
I was hoping
you two would enjoy working together.
(STUTTERS) What's with the blinking?
It's Morse code.
So we can talk about...
Without hurting... Feelings.
Uh, Sheldon, I don't know Morse code.
I do. And if you have something to say,
you can say it to my face.
Oh.
All right.
I'm a little rusty,
could you say that again?
(EXHALES)
She's going to be home at "8:00-ish"?
(STAMMERS) What is that? 8:01, 8:02?
And what kind of scientist uses "ish"?
I'll give it a go.
My ride home with you was hellish.
Sheldon, honey, if you wanna join us
for dinner you're more than welcome.
Oh, thank you. I don't think
I'd be very good company tonight.
Hmm, well, then out you go.
Okay, what is going on?
Well, ever since
Amy started working with Howard
she hasn't been home.
Didn't that just start this morning?
And has she been home?
You know, that would frustrate me.
Does it frustrate you?
It does.
I get that.
You know, it's okay to feel frustrated
when things aren't going your way.
(SIGHS) I suppose.
Ah, maybe it's not that big a deal.
No, no, no, your feelings are valid.
Now, why don't you go wash up
and we'll call you when dinner's ready.
Okay.
(DOOR CLOSES)
What did you do? Are you a witch?
Well, I've been reading
Bernadette's parenting book.
It's like the answer key
to the Sheldon test.
That's amazing.
I know. But, you know,
it's only birth to five.
What do we do when he turns six?
Take him to the zoo and leave him there.
Hey, Bernadette.
Oh, hey, Raj. Howard's not here.
I know. He's been at the lab every night
this week with his work wife.
That's weird, I thought his work wife
was standing in my kitchen.
Don't be snippy, I came to see
how you were doing.
Like, uh, do you need
help with anything?
Thank you.
There are a few things around the house
that I've been waiting for Howard
to get to. The smoke alarms need--
No, I meant emotionally.
How are you feeling?
Like you're not really here to help me.
Wow, still snippy.
Everything's fine.
Howard's really excited about his work,
he's been in a great mood.
I'm really proud of him.
And I can fit into the pants
I wore in high school.
Come on,
we don't need to lie to each other.
You're right. I have a teething baby,
I'm pregnant, I have a proposal
due tomorrow,
I don't have time to hear about
how much you're missing my husband.
Well, I think I know why
he's been working so late.
- Hi.
- Welcome home.
- How was work?
-(CHUCKLES) Great.
- Howard had an idea for--
- That's enough about work.
You just got here. You need to sit down
and let me pamper you.
Oh. (CHUCKLES)
Well, that sounds nice.
I got you a little something
to help you relax.
Sheldon, that is the sweetest--
Wha-- What is this?
The notes from our
quantum cognition project.
I thought we could spend the evening
grinding away on it.
(SIGHS) ljust got home. I'm tired.
Of Howard. I know.
So how about you and me
make some beautiful science together?
Sheldon, I want
to work on this with you,
just not tonight.
What if we get up early
and do it in the morning?
I promise I'll be way more into it.
You know what?
There was a time
that you would have been happy
to stay up and collaborate
all night with me
and then wake up in the morning
and do it some more.
(SIGHS) Fine, but can we make it quick?
No. If you're just going to make me
do all the work, then go to bed.
But don't be surprised if you walk
out here and catch me doing it myself.
Ugh.
Sheldon's texting me
to drive him to Bernadette's.
What are you gonna say?
Well, they did just introduce
the middle finger emoji.
If it's not for this,
I don't know what it's for.
No, no, no. He'll just think that means,
"Be there in a minute."
But-- maybe there's something
in the book that will help.
Worth a shot.
Okay, let's see, let's see.
"Biting other children?"
Sometimes, but problem for another day.
Okay, wait, wait, here we go.
"Let him have ownership of his choices.
"Allow him to choose from options
that are acceptable to you."
All right. I'll give it a try.
I can drive you in two hours, or
you can take an Uber.
Good. See, now he feels like
he has a choice.
(CELL PHONE CHIMES)
He's gonna take an Uber.
It worked.
Unless he bites the driver, yeah.
And now they're working on a Saturday.
Can you believe them?
I mean, is this how
you envisioned your weekend?
No, it is not.
This whole thing is maddening.
I'm really busy.
I don't have time
to listen to you complain.
Hey, you're complaining too.
"Sheldon, why are you here?"
"Sheldon, the applesauce
is for the baby."
What do you want?
ljust wish I could make
Howard feel as angry as I'm feeling.
Well, maybe you could do something
he likes and make him jealous.
- Like what?
- Have you ever read Tom Sawyer?
- No.
- Chores. He likes chores.
Ooh, what kind of chores?
Well, you could change the batteries
in the smoke detectors.
That would drive him crazy.
That's great.
Oh, he'll be so mad
smoke will be coming out of his ears
and then the smoke detectors
will detect it.
Wait a minute, hold on.
Why'd you ask me about Tom Sawyer?
I'm just interested in you.
Wha-- You are sweeter
than your applesauce.
Okay, I'm going to extend the wait time
and have it poll the A to D converter
at the top of the loop
instead of the bottom.
Ah, that's impressive.
You think that's impressive,
take apart that brain model.
(GASPS)
Oh, my God, three of clubs,
that was my card.
How did you...
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
I used make it appear in my pants,
but HR said I had to stop doing that.
So, how much longer till we can test it?
It needs to compile,
so it's gonna be a few minutes. (SIGHS)
Sounds like we've
earned ourselves a break.
Wanna hear some Neil Sedaka?
You know,
that's your greatest magic trick
'cause you just read my mind.
(BOTH LAUGH)
(NEIL SEDAKA'S "CALENDAR GIRL" PLAYING)
(BOTH SINGING)
Well, well, well.
- Hi.
- Hey.
You say you're busy as bees,
yet here you are, dancing.
Although, I suppose bees do dance,
but their dance lets other bees know
where the pollen is,
and yours does not. So my logic,
despite that slight detour, does track.
We're just waiting
for my code to compile.
What are you doing here?
I stopped by to see if you wanted
to go to the movies with me.
Oh, (STUTTERS) I'd love to,
but we're just about to test
the interface. It could take a while.
Okay, buddy, this is not my place,
but Bernadette's been feeling
a little abandoned
with all the hours
you've been putting in.
You just asked him to go to the movies.
Yeah, but our weird relationship
was grandfathered into their marriage,
and yours was not.
Okay, I put new batteries
in the smoke detectors.
Did you do the laundry?
Hmm, I sure did.
Ooh, he's gonna be steamed,
just like his dress shirts.
At least he can still clean the oven,
so that's something.
Oh, that's what he thinks.
Where's your steel wool?
Right here.
We make quite the team.
Sure do.
Guys, you won't believe this.
I stopped by the university
to check in on Howard and Amy
and they were having fun.
Well, don't worry.
He won't be having any fun
when he gets home.
I did all his favorite chores.
What are you talking about?
Howard hates doing chores.
Yeah, then why would
Bernadette tell me that--
(GASPS) Bernadette.
Did you play on my well-established
gullibility to clean your house?
Sure did.
Well, I would storm out of here,
but I already have
the gloves and the steel wool
and I really do love
cleaning an oven. Move.
She made me do all her chores
and it wasn't even her idea.
She stole it from Tom Sawyer.
You know what? This is crazy.
Howard and Amy are working together,
get over it.
Leonard, what are you doing?
"Knowing when to say when."
This is not a big deal.
It is a big deal.
Howard's getting Amy used to
laughing and listening to music.
What if she expects
that madness at home?
You know, that is a good point.
I'm really proud of the way you're
able to talk express your feelings.
Thank you. I'm just so angry.
You know, everyone gets angry.
Even mommies and daddies.
You can't think this is the right time
to validate his behavior.
Okay, what about
"presenting a united front"?
What about you coddling him,
and he's never gonna learn?
Look.
You sound frustrated,
and I'm really proud of the way
you're able to state your opinion.
Thank you. Wait, no, no!
Don't use that book on me!
Wait, what book?
(SIGHS) Penny's been using one of
Bernadette's parenting books on you.
What? So has he.
What makes you think
you can treat me like a child?
Your shampoo comes in a Big Bird bottle.
That's because the adult shampoo
burns my man eyes.
Hey, what are you working on?
Oh, my God. You're still here?
Of course I'm here.
I know what you're going through.
Really? You have a needy
Indian man in your house?
I did, but then he came over here.
So is this how it's gonna be
if we have kids,
you're just gonna
throw me under the bus?
Well, if you spoil them
the way you do Sheldon, then yeah.
Uh, my way was working, okay.
I think you're just upset because
there are some things
I'm better than you at.
Well, you can't end a sentence
with a preposition,
so clearly not grammar.
If you're so smart,
was that a smart thing to say?
That depends. Before I said it,
was sex tonight still on the table?
- No.
- Then it's fine.
You know, once we get this operational,
we could probably figure out
how to make it wireless.
That'd be amazing.
(CELL PHONE CHIMES)
Oh, it's Sheldon.
Oh, he's upset with Leonard and Penny.
(CELL PHONE CHIMES)
And Bernadette.
And Mark Twain.
Yeah, Bernadette texted earlier.
Raj is really getting on her nerves.
I guess we have been working late a lot.
(EXHALES)
Should we call it a night and go home?
Or we could brew a pot of coffee
and power through.
I don't know, it's getting kinda late.
Hey, where's my watch?
Why don't you ask your skeleton?
(AMY GASPS)
Oh, my God, how is that even possible?
This is great,
the two of us hanging out.
Why didn't we think of this earlier?
Agreed. I don't need Amy
to watch a movie,
I can not hold your hand just as easily.
(CHUCKLES)
In the book this is based on,
that man's the killer.
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
English - SDH