But why do they still call Batman
using the Bat-Signal?
Wouldn't it just be, like,
easier to text him?
The Bat-Signal
isn't just to alert Batman,
it's also to strike fear
in the hearts of his enemies
and let them know he's coming.
Sort of like Sheldon's knock. (CHUCKLES)
Comparing me to Batman? I'll take it.
If we don't do anything how long do you
think they'll talk about Batman?
Well, I've known them for 11 years,
so 11 years.
I believe they do text him.
The Bat-Signal is linked
to his phone via Bluetooth.
Has that been in the comics?
No, it's just what I believe.
All right, I'm putting a stop to this.
If you knew how,
why'd you wait eleven years?
Hey, guys, guess what?
Today at work I found out
I'm going to meet Bill Gates.
(ALL GASPING)
Sorry, Leonard,
you and Penny had a good run.
I'm not leaving him for Bill Gates.
Are you sure?
I bet his internet's really fast
How did this happen?
Well, his foundation is looking to
partner with a pharmaceutical company
to help develop affordable vaccines,
so they asked me to show him around.
That's great, when's he coming?
He gets in on Sunday, and Monday morning
I'm gonna give him a tour
of the labs and offices.
Oh.
He gets in on Sunday, April 1st.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY) Nice try, Penny.
What are you talking about?
April Fools' Day.
This is another one of your classic
pranks you try to pull on me every year.
Literally never pulled a prank on you.
Oh, really? What about last year,
when you sent me that email
with the photo attached
but you didn't attach a photo?
That was a mistake.
Messing with me, yes, it was.
And this year, I'm not falling for it.
- Sheldon, I swear--
-(EXCLAIMS) What are you doing?
Oh, you're right.
He's not coming. April Fools.
You know what they say,
fool me N times,
where N equals the amount of times
you've already fooled me, shame on you.
Fool me N plus one times, shame on me.
(THEME SONG PLAYING)
So you're gonna spend a day
with Bill Gates, I'm a little jealous.
I'm a little nervous.
You know if I do a good job,
I'm hoping they'll consider me
for a PR position that's opening up.
Well, if you're nervous...
(STUTTERS) I know a lot about him,
I can fill you in
or maybe come along, whatever.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
I think I'll be okay.
Well, I'm just saying, what are you
gonna do when he wants to talk about
high-level language interpreters
for microcomputers?
What are high-level language
interpreters for micro-computers?
A way of programming computers
using words and commands
instead of binary code.
Oh, that's actually kind of interesting,
tell me more.
- Oh, well--
- That, I'll do that.
I didn't even see it coming.
Yeah, well, you never do.
(STUTTERS) Look,
it's just, he's an idol of mine
and I would love the chance
to hang out with him.
Look, I know you want to meet him but
I can't turn this into a social thing,
okay, this is my job,
I really need it to go well.
I get it, I get it, you're right.
Actually, I've already met him
once before.
He gave a talk at Princeton
and my mom took me.
Oh, really? Was he nice?
He was super nice.
I got pretty emotional
and started crying
and he didn't make fun
of me or anything.
Well, you were a kid.
Uh-huh.
Bye, my babies, I love you.
(MIMICKING CHILDREN)
We love you too, Mommy.
Yeah, don't do that.
AMY: Bernadette?
Hi. Where are you off to?
El parque.
"El Parque?"
Learning Spanish
so I can talk to the other nannies.
(CHUCKLES)
How's that going?
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
(IN ENGLISH) Good?
Oh.
(STUTTERS)
No bueno.
- Thanks for coming over.
- No problem.
Can I get you anything?
Juice box? 'Naners?
'Naners?
(GRUNTS) Sorry. Mom brain.
I think I forgot how to talk
to grown-ups.
I meant ba-naners.
- You know what, I'm good.
- Okay.
-(INDISTINCT CHATTER ON TV)
- So what are we watching?
Bob the Builder. I'll catch you up.
That one's Bob.
He's a builder.
Isn't this a kid's show?
It's what we watch in this house.
Bob the Builder,
Dinosaur Train and Peppa Pig,
which is both funny and meaningful.
You wanna take a break
and maybe get something to eat?
Sure.
Why does it not feel like we're going?
Hang on, ljust want to see
if Bob can fix it.
(CHUCKLES) Yes, he can.
Oh, hey.
I folded your laundry for you.
You're welcome.
Uh, that's not mine.
You're saying that these aren't yours?
No.
So you're saying that I'm touching
a stranger's underpants?
Yes.
And just like that
it's the worst day of my life.
- Hey, why are you being so weird?
-(SIGHS)
It occurred to me that perhaps you were
telling the truth about Bill Gates
and it wasn't just
part of an elaborate prank.
What would the prank part even be?
I show up to meet Bill Gates
over your "objections"
but it's not Bill Gates at all,
no, it's one of those look-a-likes
that you hire for a party
and then when I go around
showing everybody the balloon animal
that Bill Gates made for me,
I look like an idiot.
Have you been eating laundry detergent?
I just need you to tell me the truth.
This is driving me crazy.
Sheldon, he is really coming.
- Is he?
- He is.
- Really?
- Yeah.
(SIGHS)
Well, now I don't know what to believe.
Thanks for getting me out of the house,
I feel like my brain is turning to mush.
Happy to help.
Did I show you the video
of the kids sitting?
Yes, you texted it to me at 3:00 a.m.
(CHUCKLES)
Thought someone
was either in jail or dead. (CHUCKLES)
I'm sorry.
No, no, it gave me something to watch
while I tried to go back to sleep.
You know what, I don't wanna be
one of those moms
who can only talk about her kids.
Okay, well,
I'm reading a pretty good book.
It's the untold story of female artists
during the Renaissance.
Oh, I'm in the middle of a book too,
it's three pages long
and it floats in the bath.
All right. We can talk about
something else.
It also quacks when you squeeze it,
you should've seen Michael laugh.
I think I have a video.
Or maybe we can't.
(VIDEO GAME SOUND EFFECTS)
Why is your screen name "John Williams?"
Uh, because I always score.
Hey. I think I'm gonna head
to the office for a little bit.
On a Sunday?
Yeah, just wanna make sure
I'm prepared for tomorrow.
Do you think you could get Bill Gates
to sign something for me?
Yeah, maybe, like what?
My arm, my chest, his call.
His call will be to the police.
Penny, remember when I introduced you
to hundred calorie Dove Bars
and you said you owed me,
like, big time?
Guys, even if I wanted
to introduce you,
there is no room in his schedule.
I mean, look at this itinerary.
I meet him at his hotel
first thing tomorrow morning,
and then we're on the go all day long.
You're right. Guys, this is her job,
we need to respect that.
Thank you, honey.
Proud of you.
Love you.
I totally just saw
what hotel he's staying at.
What are we waiting here for?
For Penny to walk down the stairs,
get in her car and drive away.
Right, smart. (CLEARS THROAT)
That long enough?
She's pretty quick, let's go.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
What would you do
if you had a billion dollars?
Same as Bill Gates,
try to make the world a better place,
but I'd do it
in a working Iron Man suit.
I didn't know that came
in a boys medium.
(STUTTERS) This is a bad idea,
maybe we should go.
What are you talking about?
(STUTTERS) I don't know,
I'm just feeling guilty
like I'm kinda sneaking around
behind Penny's back.
We're not doing anything wrong.
We're just hanging out in a hotel
lobby, plenty of people do that.
The businessmen,
the high-end prostitutes.
That's a fun new game, CEO or ho.
No, this is wrong, let's go.
Guys, guys, that's him. Be cool.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Cooler.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
(STUTTERS) Mr. Gates,
I'm Doctor Leonard Hofstadter,
we've actually met before.
Sorry, I don't remember.
You were so nice... (STUTTERS)
And it was really special to me
because you've been
such a big influence on my life.
I mean, ever since I was a little kid,
I've looked up to you like a hero.
Oh, now I remember.
Would you like a tissue?
How about a hug?
How about a tissue?
Sorry I talked about my kids
the whole time.
Oh, don't worry about it.
I mean, besides you cutting up
my meat for me, it was a lovely lunch.
God, what's happening?
I'm a smart, educated, successful...
(STAMMERS)
Woman?
I was gonna get it.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
Pregnancy and childbirth
actually cause physical changes
to the structure of your brain.
I liked the old structure of my brain.
But then I liked
a lot of my old structures.
Well, these are positive changes.
Studies with rats show that new mothers
are more sensitive to danger,
better at multitasking
and bolder in the pursuit of food.
I did stick a couple
of lamb chops in my purse.
So that's what I was smelling.
Look, even though your brain
is different, in many ways it's better.
But were you bored?
Of course not.
You're lying.
Which you can tell
because your maternal brain
is better at sensing non-verbal cues.
Now you're just being condescending.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Look at you, two-for-two.
LEONARD: Hold the door, hold the door.
Oh, hi, Leonard.
Didn't you hear me yell "hold the door"?
I did. But you know what they say,
"hold the door, get robbed some more."
No one says that.
Oh. Well, they should
because it's true and it rhymes.
So, where have you been?
Actually, I met Bill Gates.
(SIGHS)
I see, you're all in on it,
ah, nice try.
It's not an April Fools' joke, Sheldon.
I actually went to a hotel and met him.
Right, right. Okay, so, "Bill Gates"
was at the "hotel" that you "went to."
Why is "went to" in quotes?
Fine. So "Bill Gates" was at the "hotel"
that you went to.
That's you and Bill Gates.
It is.
- Were you crying?
- No.
So it wasn't a joke
and I actually could have met him?
He's probably still there.
(GASPS) What hotel?
The La Quinta Inn in Thousand Oaks
under the name Hernandez.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
April Fools.
(KEYS CLATTER)
- Hey.
- Hey. Where have you been?
Ah, just hanging out with the guys.
They still mad at me?
Uh, they were,
but then I was like, "Hey."
And they were like, "What?"
and I was like, "You know,"
and they were like, "Okay. "
You're a good husband.
Well, it's not for me to say but you
just said it so you're probably right.
Well, as it turns out,
there is a little reception
for Mr. Gates tomorrow night, I asked
if I could bring you and they said yes.
What?
Yeah, you get to meet Bill Gates again.
Wait, what do you mean again?
'Cause you met him
that one time with your mom.
Yes.
And then again tomorrow for
a total of two and only two times.
Yeah, I wonder if he'll remember you.
Yeah, I wonder that too.
BERNADETTE: (THROUGH SPEAKERS}
The sun is losing about six times ten
to the twelfth grams per second
so the fraction of the mass
it loses every year
is about ten to the negative thirteenth.
But don't worry,
it'll be millions of years
before we all freeze to death.
Sweet dreams.
Wow. Hop on Pop took
a dark turn there at the end.
Amy made me realize
that new mothers are cognitively primed
to take in new information,
and I've been wasting it
making up songs about our babies' toes.
To be fair I co-wrote
Pinky Toe Pinky Toe.
Evolution gave me this mom brain
to focus on the baby,
but I figure I can hack it
to learn all kinds of new things.
That's great.
Yeah, there was a problem
and I fixed it.
Like, Bob the Builder
in that giraffe cage.
Spoiler alert,
I didn't see that one yet.
So that's fun,
you get to meet Bill Gates again.
It's not fun, I'm screwed.
It's fun for us. (CHUCKLES)
Maybe he won't remember you.
I snotted on his tie.
Yeah, you did, like a lot.
Hello, Leonard.
I thought I'd find you here.
You snake.
What's going on?
He sent me all the way to Thousand Oaks
to meet Bill Gates
when he knew full well
he wasn't staying there.
Leonard, that's terrible.
Yeah, why would you do that?
You know he's staying
at the Double Tree in Long Beach.
Ah-ha.
Wait, how do I know
you're not tricking me?
We probably are.
(SIGHS)
But what if we're not?
You think you're so smart.
You think I'm going to fall for it
again, don't you?
Well, I won't.
- Where you going?
- Shut up.
Aw, you sure you can't come?
I want to but I'm just too sick.
(PENNY SIGHS)
You really wanted to meet him.
I know. I've been trying to hide it,
so I could go
but I don't wanna make him sick.
You know, you do look
pretty pale and clammy.
Yeah.
Have fun.
Well, feel better, okay.
No, that's just my regular
pale and clammy.
I mean, really the bigger danger
isn't the loss of mass
instead it will run out of hydrogen
to use for nuclear fuel,
swell up into a red giant
and fry the Earth.
So you don't want to split a salad?
No, thank you.
But speaking of splitting things,
did you hear about
the light-splitting greenhouse film
that could improve
photosynthetic efficiency?
No. (SIGHS)
Just a little something I read while
nursing a human being that I made.
- L'm just gonna get the chicken.
- Ah.
N-E-K-C-I-H-C.
Chicken backwards boom, mom brain.
And a whole bottle of wine.
Oh, oh, oh. Oh, in your face. (LAUGHS)
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Hello.
Oh, hey sweetie, how ya feeling?
Oh, okay, I'm just resting.
Well, I have a surprise
that might make you feel better.
Oh, really?
Yeah, look who's here.
Wait, I know you.
No, you don't.
Yes, I do. You were waiting for me
at my hotel.
You ruined my tie.
Wait, what? What's he talking about?
Uh...
He obviously, he's kidding. (CHUCKLES)
(STUTTERS) That's a good one Bill,
I gotta go.
SHELDON: Stupid Leonard
meeting stupid Bill Gates
without stupid me.
Aw.
I'm so sorry... Sheldon?
Leonard, I can't stay mad at you.
Apology accepted.
What's for dinner? I'm starving.
(SPEAKING IN SPANISH)
(NANNIES CONVERSING IN SPANISH)
(IN ENGLISH) How are you ladies doing?
Raise your hands, if you're bueno.
(CHUCKLES)
(SPEAKING IN SPANISH)
Mi Ilamo Stuart Bloom.
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
English - SDH