What're you doing?
Pigeon check for Sheldon.
North side's all clear.
Great. Let's look at some planets.
Hey, Why'd you lug your telescope
all the way over here?
Leonard has one in our apartment.
(SARCASTICALLY) Yeah, I'm gonna
use Leonard's.
Might as well hold my hand up like this
and squint.
I don't know, it seemed pretty good.
You know, once when the cable went out
I watched an entire episode of
The Bachelor on the TV
across the street.
This one's more of a professional model.
So was the girl he picked!
This baby's got a 10-inch diameter
with F-10 ACF optics.
And tonight,
Mercury is at its highest elongation.
It makes far away things seem close,
and Mercury is a planet.
I know Mercury is a planet.
But the other thing was helpful.
Oh, look at that.
Neil Gaiman tweeted about my store.
What did he say?
"Next time you're in Pasadena,
check out The Comic Center.
"Great vibe, old school,
the owner really knows his stuff."
Isn't that amazing?
Well, it's no Sandman
but I guess we can't expect everything
he writes to be a masterpiece.
When was he in your store?
I have no idea.
I think I would remember that.
Obviously vibranium
is the most powerful metal in comics.
More powerful than adamantium?
Mmm. He's right, Wolverine's claws,
Ultron's outer shell, need I go on?
You don't need to,
but you probably will.
What about Wonder Woman's bracelets?
Good point. Strong as a metal
and fierce as a fashion choice.
You know,
Thor's hammer is pretty powerful,
and in the comics
it's made out of enchanted uru.
Yeah. I think it's the enchantment
that's powerful
and not the Uru, but thanks for playing.
Oh, man! I can't believe Neil Gaiman
came in and we weren't even there.
No.
(THEME SONG PLAYING)
Can you see Mercury? Can you see it?
One second.
You know the
Greek version of Mercury, Hermes,
was worshiped in Athens by the
carving of giant wooden phalluses.
Please, Amy, get your mind
out of the ancient Athenian gutter.
Got another follower, I'm blowing up.
- Great, how many does that make?
- High double digits.
- The nineties?
- Mid double digits.
Hey, uh, Penny,
you wanna check this out?
Yeah. Sure.
All right. Just look through here
and if you wanna take a picture
just push that button.
Okay. Oh, what is that?
Is it Mercury?
I'm really jonesing for Mercury.
I think it's a little early
for Mercury to be visible yet.
Playing hard to get.
I like that in a planet.
No, there's something fuzzy.
Is it your teen years?
No. Yes. Shut up. Look, I--
No really, I think I see something.
Well, it could just be your eyelash.
It's not an eyelash.
Okay, well, take a picture. Let's see.
Okay. Here.
Hmm.
- I do see something.
- Told ya.
- What is it?
- I don't know. Maybe it's a comet.
That would be so cool.
You guys wanna see a real star,
look over here.
What?
I just got retweeted by
Patton 0swalt's brother.
So, this is really
where Neil Gaiman shops?
Neil Gaiman, Nicholas Cage,
Natalie Portman, the list goes on.
They all come here?
Unless I'm lying.
Who are all these people?
What- Wait is this a flash mob?
Are they dancing?
I don't know what
today's dancing looks like.
Hey, guys. That tweet actually
got people to come in. Isn't that great?
No. I like the way the store was before.
You mean empty and sad?
Yes, it was perfect.
Like a funeral home
that sells Pokemon cards.
What am I supposed to do now if
I wanna hang out and read a comic book?
Go sit on the couch.
A... Next to a stranger?
I say, if I'm gonna sit,
read and ignore a woman,
it's gonna be my fiancée.
Why're you being such a baby
about the crowds?
You go to Comic Con.
You- I'm sorry. You're comparing
this place to Comic Con?
What- Can I go to the bathroom here,
next to a Wookiee
who got his zipper stuck in his fur?
Wow, we go to Comic Con
for different reasons.
You know... Just...
Get me a copy of Action Comics #1,000,
and I'll be on my way.
Sorry, all out.
Now you just let people
come in and buy them?
Oh, so I didn't realize
your soul was also for sale.
Well, it wasn't. But make me an offer.
(PHONE CHIMING)
- Who is that?
- Sheldon.
- Who's he mad at?
- Neil Gaiman.
- Who's that?
- Not us.
Oh, great.
- Guys.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- So guess what.
That indeed was a comet last night,
and it turns out
no one's seen it before.
- Wow!
- What? Really?
Look at that,
ljust discovered a comet. Oh!
What do you mean, you discovered it?
Well, I'm the one who saw it.
In my telescope, that I positioned.
All you did was look into it.
You both discovered it.
You can put both your names
on the registration form.
- Actually we can't.
- Why not?
Because when I filled it out,
it asked for name of discoverer
and I put Rajesh Koothrappali,
because, because that's who I am
and that's what I did.
Are you kidding me?
Well, he is the one
who knew it was a comet.
No he didn't,
he thought it was an eyelash.
And you thought it was a fuzzy streak.
I mean, do you even know
what a comet is?
Yeah. The thing I saw first.
I honestly don't think that
that qualifies as a discovery.
But I took the picture.
Because I told you to.
Like, if a monkey took the picture,
did it discover the comet?
Excuse me?
He didn't mean monkey.
Get the hell out of my apartment!
She didn't mean that-
Actually, I think she did,
you should go.
- You look great.
- Thanks.
Would you believe this is actually
a dress from before I was pregnant?
Well, it's not a competition
but I wore this suit to my Bar Mitzvah.
Where's Stuart? I told him
we had a 6:30 reservation.
I don't know. I'll call him.
(PHONE RINGING)
Comic Center,
where the real superhero is you.
Stuart, you're supposed
to be babysitting.
Oh, shoot! That was tonight.
I forgot, the store's been really busy.
Well, when can you get here?
Um, I don't think I can. Listen to this.
I was ringing up a customer
and I heard someone say,
"Hey, there's a line,"
and I looked, and there was.
Come on. You can't do this to us.
I am really sorry,
I will make it up to you.
But it won't be with
a Val Kilmer Batman figurine
because some
sucker's buying that right now.
(CHUCKLING)
Not you, this is great.
He says he has to work.
Oh, it's okay, we can have
date night another night.
But you got all dressed up.
We were supposed to
have dinner and romance.
We'll just have to divide and conquer.
I'll go to dinner and you can stay home
with the internet and have romance.
Okay, look, I googled it.
I took the picture,
so it's my discovery.
He stole my comet.
I know. But on the other hand,
do you really care?
Yes, I care.
This happens to me all the time.
People take one look at me and assume
I don't know what I'm talking about.
Mmm, I'm sure that's not true.
I'm sorry, are you saying
I don't know what I'm talking about?
No, I'm not saying anything ever again.
Look, I'm serious.
The other day at work,
I had this great idea.
But no one was listening to me,
and then five minutes later
Paul said the same thing
and they practically
carried him around the room.
Oh, well, what was it?
Well, CPK for lunch
but that's just one example.
It also happens with all the doctors
I have to deal with,
you know, they're so condescending.
I'm so sick of letting this stuff slide.
I found that comet.
Why shall I let Raj say he found it?
I know you're right but he is our friend
and this could be good for his career.
Wait. So you agree with me
but he still gets his way?
There you go. Everybody wins.
My God, you're such a people pleaser.
You can't stand making anyone angry.
Why would I want to make anyone angry?
'Cause it would mean
you were on my side.
Oh, I am on your side.
Hey, let's not forget
who you're really mad at here.
Raj. Oh and Paul. Paul sucks, right?
But don't tell him I said that.
Hey, Howard. Did you see the-
(EXCLAIMING IN SHOCK)
I'm over here, Sheldon.
Oh! That was a close one.
I almost went home with that guy.
You doing okay? Do we need to go?
No, I'm fine.
I admit, all these people
did take me by surprise at first.
But I've learnt that
I can accept change.
Since when?
I managed it when
Amy switched her shampoo
from Prell to Prell for oily hair.
Although, I do miss the way her head
used to slide off the pillow.
- May I help you?
- Who are you?
Oh, I'm Denise.
The new assistant manager.
Nope.
Can you believe it?
In the past decade I have spent
thousands of dollars in that store.
And this is the thanks I get.
You're right, I mean,
he could at least get you a mug.
He gave me a mug.
What do you think I'm drinking out of?
Oh, do you even pay attention?
Honestly, less and less.
Amy, the comic book store is like
my version of the country
in Black Panther.
Okay, I'm afraid this is gonna get
really offensive to certain groups.
But go on.
The nation of Wakanda was a hidden gem
and they wanted to keep it that way
because they knew
if they opened it up to the world,
everything that was special about it
would get ruined.
- Are you done?
- Yes.
(SIGHING IN RELIEF) Okay! That both
made sense and wasn't offensive.
And to make things worse,
Stuart hired some woman.
There we go.
Yep. No.
I'm not annoyed that she's a woman.
I'm annoyed and she's a woman.
No, I get that.
I'm annoyed and I'm a woman.
It's just, Stuart knows
my likes and dislikes
and I can count on his discretion
if I pick up the occasional back issue
of Superman's pal, Jimmy Olsen.
Which I don't.
Well, don't think of her as a stranger.
Just think of her as a friend
you haven't berated,
lectured or condescended to yet.
I hadn't thought of it that way.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I mean, you're wise
and you smell like books.
You really are the whole package.
Raj, just help me out.
Penny's pretty mad
about this comet thing.
Well, I'm sorry she's upset.
But she didn't discover it.
Come on. You know she was a part of it.
Just add her name to the registration.
But I already told everyone at work
that I did it.
My boss was so excited
he started calling me Captain Comet,
which is better than
his last nickname for me, Doctor Donuts,
because one time I had two donuts.
And two times I had three donuts.
I guess you're just gonna
have to swallow your pride.
I... I can't do that.
Sure you can.
Just pretend it's two or three donuts.
You don't understand, Leonard,
I need this.
My last big discovery was
if you press your upper lip hard enough,
you can block a sneeze.
I told you that.
This is all my fault.
I brought this upon myself.
I'm a bad scientist.
I'm a selfish person.
No, no, don't get upset.
You're not a bad person.
Just let me talk to Penny.
I'm sure I can make her understand.
Thank you.
You're a good friend, Leonard.
(SIGHING) I'm glad you think so,
'cause I may be living here soon.
Just look at her, over there.
She just started and
she gets to put up "Staff Picks."
I've been coming here over ten years,
I still can't put up "Sheldon Dislikes."
I talked to her yesterday,
she really seems to know her stuff.
Challenge accepted.
That is not what that was.
Excuse me, I was wondering
if you could recommend something.
Oh, sure.
You wanna tell me what you like?
I would not.
All right, well you're wearing
a Green Lantern shirt
so I'm guessing you're a DC fan,
although that's from the Alan Scott era
so you're probably not super
into the current run.
How would you
feel about an alternate history
where World War One was fought
with dragons and magic?
That's what I wanted the theme
of my tenth birthday party to be.
Here. Check this out,
it's by Kurt Busiek.
You know, if you're interested
in alternate histories,
Neil Gaiman wrote one called 1602.
I'm sorry,
we're in the middle of something here.
It is pretty good, actually.
He takes the Marvel superheroes and
he puts them into Elizabethan England.
Let me guess, everyone thinks
the X-Men are the witches?
Yeah.
Why don't you take this home,
and if you don't like it,
return it,
and I'll give you your money back.
Just don't tell Stuart.
Stuart who?
Hey, where have you been?
(SIGHING) I went to yell at Raj.
And? ls he gonna give me back my comet?
Interesting thing.
Did you cave?
Maybe I did, or... Maybe I did.
But I did realize something.
(STAMMERS) I don't need
to fight your battles.
You, you are a strong
and independent woman,
you have your own voice.
And to quote another strong woman,
Katy Perry,
"It's time to hear you roar."
Did you just think of that
on your way home?
What do you want from me?
The song was on in the car.
But it doesn't mean it's not true.
Well, you make a good point.
I'm gonna go talk to Raj myself.
I know I don't say it enough,
but you go, girl.
That was enough.
What's all this?
Well, we missed our date night
and Stuart's working again.
So, I thought we could have
a date night here at home.
Why, that's so sweet.
Oh, so, is that really
what you're wearing to our date night?
Well, Stuart's not here
and the kids are sleeping.
I can wear nothing.
You might wanna hold off on that.
We're starting with soup.
Hey!
Wha- I thought you were
working late again.
I was but Denise has got it covered.
Oh, the funniest thing happened today.
You know, the receipt tape
in the cash register, it ran out.
(CHUCKLING) I didn't even know
it could do that.
You know,
we were just sitting down to dinner.
Oh! Perfect timing. I'll go wash up.
There goes date night.
Are you kidding? Stuart's here,
get your purse, we're going out.
What about the dinner you made?
Right. Well, hey, Stuart!
That can of soup sittin' by the stove,
that's for you.
You made canned soup for date night?
And you wore sweat pants. Let's go.
Oh, and it turns out
Denise is also really excited
for Dan Slott's run on Iron Man
because he was her
favorite Spider-Man writer too.
How about that?
Oh, and guess who goes to
art school right here in Pasadena?
Hmm, I don't know. Denise?
You're a good guesser, Amy.
Not as good as Denise though.
She thought
I would like this comic, Arrowsmith,
and she was right.
Well, was the store crowded?
I bet it was, I know you hate that.
Yeah, It was.
But if it weren't for the crowds
Stuart never would have hired Denise,
and she's the best.
- You must be Denise.
- Oh, yeah. How can I help you?
I'm Amy, Sheldon's fiancée.
Oh. I gotta be honest,
I wasn't a hundred percent sure
you were real.
Oh, I am.
And I heard you and Sheldon had
a great time today
talking about comic books.
We did.
Great, here's what's gonna happen.
You're gonna teach me how to do that.
- Do what?
- Pretend to like comic books.
Oh, no. I actually like comic books.
All right, let's not
get hung up on semantics,
it's late, we got a lot of work to do.
(KNOCKING AT DOOR)
I'm sorry.
I haven't even said anything yet.
I know but I heard
your footsteps coming up the stairs
and they sounded angry.
They are angry. I'm mad at you.
And you have every right to be.
Okay. I was... I was being a jerk.
We did this together
and I hogged all of the credit.
And after you've been
such a good friend to me over the years.
Like, I wouldn't even be able to
talk to women if it wasn't for you.
So... so, I'm... I'm gonna make sure
that your name is on the comet.
Thank you.
Even if it's
professionally embarrassing, you know.
Or maybe put me on thin ice at work.
I may lose my funding.
Still, uh, still wanna make this right.
Good. Bye.
That worked way better with Leonard.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Why are you reading a comic book?
Denise recommended it to me.
It's the Rebirth Omnibus.
She thought it would be a good
entry point for me into the DC universe.
And I have to say,
I really do like how-
You know, Amy... Amy, I've talked
a lot about comic books lately.
Can we talk about something else?
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
English - SDH