Howie, slow down.
I can't. I'm not allowed to eat
for 12 hours before my surgery,
and I've only got two more minutes.
What surgery are you having?
I'm stress eating.
My best friend's getting
a vasectomy tomorrow.
And you're sad you won't be able
to bear his child?
Oh, my goodness!
If it's "vasectomy gone wrong" videos,
he's seen them all.
Including the one of the guy
who's sitting on what appears
to be a cantaloupe but is not.
And I'm done.
They're going to start making
Professor Proton's science show again.
I thought he passed away.
He did. He was cremated
and his remains were put
in a baking soda volcano.
(PENNY CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Don't make jokes.
He meant a lot to Sheldon.
Mm, me too. I grew up watching his show.
He's one of the reasons
I became a scientist.
Oh, I thought you did it
just to get girls.
Joke's on you. It worked.
Have they found anyone to replace him?
No, not yet. And it won't be easy.
Arthur Jeffries was
an accomplished scientist.
Hmm, you know who'd make
a great Professor Proton?
Meryl Streep.
She's not a scientist.
Uh, then explain to me why she has
chemistry with literally everyone.
It would be nice if they cast a woman.
Oh, (STUTTERS) you've already got
Dr. Who and the Ghostbusters.
Leave us something.
Who do you think it should be?
Um, it should be a scientist
I respect, you know.
Someone with a pleasing voice
and symmetrical facial features.
Is he talking about himself?
If he's talking,
he's talking about himself.
ljust know how much Professor Proton
touched me as a child,
and I feel that I owe it to him
to try and touch
as many children as possible.
You should put that
on your audition tape.
(THEME SONG PLAYING)
You doing okay?
No, I'm very nervous.
(MAN GROANING)
Where are you going?
- Gift shop.
- There is no gift shop. Sit down.
This was your idea.
(GRUNTS) So was having sex.
And look where that got us.
This isn't a big deal. Stop whining.
When you were in labor
and I said that, you kicked me.
Howard Wolowitz.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
- Want me to go with you?
- No.
- I'll be fine.
- Yeah, we got this.
Sit down.
(SIGHS) Wish me luck.
Other way, buster.
Okay, you ready?
Yeah, almost. I'm working on
my facial expressions.
See, I've got "interested."
Hmm.
I've got "very interested." Hmm.
And, "enraged."
Why would you be enraged?
Hmm, better to have it and not need it
than to need it and not have it.
Okay.
And rolling.
Hello, I am theoretical physicist
Doctor Sheldon Cooper,
auditioning for the role of
Professor Proton.
Now, excuse me
while I get into character.
Hello, I'm Professor Proton.
And today, boys and girls,
we're going to have fun with science.
Did you know you could calculate
the mass of an electron
using household items?
It's true. All you'll need is a pencil,
some paper, dry ice, rubbing alcohol
and a spool of 50-micron-thick
cobalt-60 wire.
And remember,
don't put it in your mouth.
Or, instead of becoming a scientist,
you'll become wildly radioactive.
Hang on. I have a question.
Do you have any experiments
that aren't life-threatening?
Come on! That was a perfect take,
and you ruined it.
Oh, look, hey! I did need "enraged."
(EXHALES)
Ow, ow, ow.
Really hurts, huh?
No, he's just saying,
"Ow can these prices be so low?"
It's gonna be okay. A day or two
of rest, and you'll be fine.
You know nothing about Jewish people.
(BABY CRYING ON BABY MONITOR)
(HOWARD GROANING)
Let me go check on her.
(HOWARD BREATHING HEAVILY)
Okay, uh, this is a bit awkward.
It says here that I need to
check the area for redness and swelling.
You know what?
It hurts so much, go ahead.
So you see, boys and girls,
H, or "helicity,"
is the natural variable
to use relativistically,
and is defined as “S dot P,"
divided by the magnitude of P.
So the next time someone
on the playground tells you,
you can only use integral values
for the matrix that determines
the spin of the antiproton,
You stop being friends with that kid,
'cause he's going nowhere.
Until next week,
this is Professor Proton saying,
"Zero one zero zero zero zero one zero
"zero One One One One zero zero One
"zero One One zero zero One zero one.
"That's 'bye"'in ASCII binary,
or 'good-binary.“
(LAUGHS)
(CHUCKLES)
So,
what do you think?
Well, I already told him
that I loved it,
but if you found it confusing,
or dangerous or,
I don't know,
three to four times too long,
now's the time to share.
I --
I don't know what to say.
Leonard, do you know what to say?
Sheldon, I thought it,
it, uh, it (STUTTERS) looked like
you were having so much fun.
Hey, that's what you used to tell me
to say to Penny
after one of her terrible plays.
- Hey!
(SIGHS)
Well, what was wrong with it?
You know, did you find it
borderline psychotic?
I mean, I liked that about it,
but you guys discuss.
(STUTTERS) Do you remember when you were
a kid and you'd watch Professor Proton?
- Of course.
- Well, did he ever make you
hate science and the people who do it?
What are you saying?
(STUTTERS)
ljust think it would be better
if your contempt for children
wasn't so much in the foreground.
You want me to lie?
(SIGHS)
Look, it's not lying, it's acting.
Sheldon Cooper may not like kids,
but Professor Proton loves them.
Interesting.
You know, I hadn't really
thought of it that way.
It's, it's similar to how, you know,
I'm afraid of dogs
but my DnD character
likes dogs. You know?
But he's allergic,
so he can't be around them.
Why don't we have a dog?
Hey, you can always reshoot it.
Hmm, I suppose.
And, you know,
maybe I could even get some tips
from someone who's acted professionally.
Oh, Sheldon, obviously,
I'd be happy to help you out.
I don't know what to say.
Hey, Sheldon, what's up?
I need an acting coach.
Oh.
Would you give me
Patrick Stewart's number?
No.
Fine. I guess you can do it.
(BELL CHIMING)
HOWARD: Bernie!
Where did you get a bell?
APP store.
(BELL CHIMING)
- Fun, let me see.
-(CHUCKLES)
When you catch me, you can have it back.
You wanna lie down, watch a movie?
I can't. I got my
16-week check-up to get to
and then I'll pick up
some Chinese for dinner.
I'll take Halley with me.
You sure you're not overdoing it?
No, it's fine.
Great, then maybe instead of Chinese,
fire up the grill
and throw on a couple of steaks?
Kung Pao chicken, please.
- Oh, boy.
- What?
They cast the new Professor Proton.
- Is it Sheldon?
- Not exactly.
SHELDON: Wheaten!
It's Wil Wheaton.
BERNADETTE: Hi.
Hey.
How was the doctor?
Good, but I have some news.
Don't say twins, don't say twins.
It's not twins.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY) Only because I would
have loved them both.
The doctor said I was overdoing it,
so, she put me on bed rest
just to be safe.
Oh, no.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
It may not look like it,
but I'm running to you.
(INSECTS TRILLING)
Hello, Arthur.
What part of "rest in peace"
don't you understand?
I suppose you're here
because you heard the news.
Sheldon, I'm a figment
of your imagination.
I don't hear news.
You're a grumpy figment.
Look. They're remaking your show
and they cast Wil Wheaton
as Professor Proton.
And the worst part is,
he's not even a scientist.
No, the worst part is
I'm sitting on a moist log.
We have to stop this
and protect your legacy.
What legacy?
My, last two seasons, I was on
Sunday morning at 5:30.
We were beat by Davey and Goliath.
I can't believe you don't care.
Believe it.
Well, I care a lot.
And Wil Wheaton
will rue the day he ever met me.
I think that's true of most people.
Hi, guys.
Wanted to check in
and see how you two were doing.
- We're okay.
- Yeah,
hanging out in bed with my wife,
thawing out some frozen peas
in my pants, living the dream.
(BABY CRYING ON BABY MONITOR)
Oh, I'll get her.
I thought Raj was helping you out.
No, he had to work.
Plus, he has a quota for the amount
of Indian servant jokes he can tolerate.
Apparently, I filled it.
Well, hey, I can get the baby.
No, Howie's got it.
He's fine. Right, Howie?
(WINCING) Never better.
Don't be silly.
I'll take the rest of the day off
and watch Halley for you.
Or we can call Stuart.
I'm sure he could close up the store,
hop on a bus and be here in no time.
He does love the bus.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Okay, hang on. You guys don't trust me
to take care of your baby?
- No. (CHUCKLES)
- No.
- HOWARD: No. (CHUCKLES)
- BERNADETTE: No.
So, I guess,
no. wens)
Wow.
It's not that we don't trust you,
it's just,
you don't seem like
much of a baby person.
Hey! Hey, hey, I can watch
your stupid baby, okay?
If she cries, I will pick her up.
If she's hungry, I'll give her a bottle.
And if she poops,
I'll light some incense.
It would be a big help.
Okay, thank you.
Trust me, you guys have
nothing to worry about.
You know, back in Nebraska,
I raised all our baby pigs right until
the day they were slaughtered.
So, unless your baby's
made of breakfast meat, she's fine.
Would you ever get a vasectomy?
Uh, in case you haven't noticed,
Indians aren't too big on birth control.
There's probably, like,
a million more of us
since we started this conversation.
(SHELDON SIGHS)
- You okay?
- No.
No. All these comments online about Wil,
they're nothing but supportive and kind.
Where's the mean, snarky Internet
that shows up every time
I get a haircut?
You know that's us, right?
Well, luckily, I got the number
of the company
who's trying to reboot the show,
so I need you all to call
and register your displeasure.
Sheldon, no one's gonna do that.
Not true. I know of three calls
they've received already.
A southern gentleman,
um, a Cockney chimney sweep,
and Mr. T. Hm.
Who, spoiler alert, pities the fool
who tries to reboot that show.
What about "tiresome lunatic with
a bad haircut"? Has he called yet?
Come on!
How many times have we banded together
to try to save a show that we loved?
(STUTTERS) Let's shake things up
and try to kill one.
Isn't the important thing
that there's a show
to get kids excited about science?
Who cares about kids and what they like?
This is about me and something I liked
when I was a kid.
What if the reboot is great?
That's even worse.
If-if I like it, I'll feel like
I'm being disloyal to Arthur.
He was a mentor and a friend,
And I won't toss him aside for some
Hollywood pretty boy like Wil Wheaton.
It's hard to argue with him.
Because he makes no sense? Yeah.
It's actually kind of nice,
you and me getting to spend
a couple days in bed together.
Yeah. Pretty soon, we're gonna have
two crying babies in the house.
(SIGHS)
I'm glad my balls hurt.
It's all their fault.
Well, let's just enjoy this quiet time
while we still got it.
Yeah. (CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Yeah, it is really quiet.
You think Penny's doing okay?
Penny? Everything all right?
Hey, all good. Dipped her pacifier
in a little bourbon,
she conked right out.
I hope you're joking.
Of course, I'm joking.
I don't share my bourbon.
She's joking.
(CHUCKLES) Definitely.
Probably.
Wil Wheaton. Wil Wheaton.
This is Sheldon, by the way.
Hi, Sheldon.
Here I found this pizza flyer
in your fence.
- Thank you.
- Okay, now you owe me a favor.
Turn down the role of Professor Proton.
(SIGHS) I don't think so.
You can't be Professor Proton.
You're not a scientist.
Well, I was never on a starship,
but pretending I was
bought me this house.
And if I'd pretended a little longer,
it would have a swimming pool.
Yeah, some things shouldn't be rebooted.
Some things were perfect
the way they were.
Uh, (STUTTERS)
like the walled city of York?
It was a delight. But New York?
(DISGUSTED GRUNT)
Did you ever consider that
maybe Arthur would be happy
to know that his show has outlived him?
I doubt it.
He was kind of a mean old crank.
Sheldon,
I promise that I will work my hardest
to make this show great,
so that a whole new generation of kids
will grow up
and they will be able to say that
Professor Proton was the reason
they got into science.
Wow.
That was very persuasive.
Thanks.
But I won't be seduced
by your acting skills
nor your movie star charisma.
There's only one Professor Proton
and he had neither of those things.
I'll give you one more chance
to bow out.
Or what?
When we first met, we were enemies.
But we worked through that
and we became friends.
Do you really wanna go back?
Honestly, it doesn't feel
very different.
I'm not leaving.
WIL: All right,
I'm gonna sic my dog on you.
You don't have a dog.
WIL: Yes, I do.
Oh, I can't tell if you're lying.
You're such a good actor.
Hey, how you doing?
What are you doing here?
Oh, ljust came by, you know,
to see if you need any help.
Howard and Bernadette
asked you to check up on me.
That is not entirely true.
So did Leonard and everybody.
How irresponsible do you all think I am?
We don't think you're irresponsible.
We think you're
fun-loving.
That is just a nice word
for irresponsible.
Hmm, you might be more on the ball
than we thought.
I'm getting a little hungry.
- Want me to get it this time?
-(SNIFFLES) Oh, that'd be great.
(BELL CHIMING)
This is fun.
And now you also get to see
an annoyed blonde walk into the room.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
What?
Can you get us a little snack?
Are you sure you don't want
your spy to do it?
What are you talking about?
You really don't trust me?
You had to have Amy stop by?
We trust you.
Yeah, you were a terrible waitress
and we still asked you
to get us a snack.
(BABY CRYING ON BABY MONITOR)
Excuse me, while I go
take care of your baby.
Then I'll bring you your snack
and you can insult me some more.
I don't know about you,
but I am not eating
whatever she brings us.
PENNY". Hey, Halley! Oh, it's okay,
Aunty Penny's here.
Shh. Let's get you changed.
Your mommy and daddy say they trust me,
but they're full of the same stuff
your diaper is.
(SIGHS) Now I feel bad.
Well, she never really liked me.
It's kind of nice
she hates you now, too.
PENNY: Oh, but I'm here for you,
and I would never let
anything happen to you
because your Aunty Penny
loves you so much.
HALLEY: Mama.
Was that her first word?
PENNY: No, no, baby, I'm not your mama.
Your mama's the nice lady
we're gonna go see right now
so I can rub this in her face.
Do you hear that, suckers?
She called me "Mama."
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
Hello, Arthur.
You know,
we could, we could also meet in a deli.
I'm sorry to say that I failed you.
I tried to stop Wil Wheaton
being Professor Proton,
but I couldn't.
See, now, that's the kind of thing
you could tell a fella over a
pastrami sandwich.
Well, don't worry,
he's now on my enemies list forever.
He's totally cut off.
Interesting.
Can anyone
sign up for that list?
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
English - SDH