RAJ: If Bruce Banner is driving
a rental car and turns into the Hulk,
do you think he's covered or
does he need to
add the Hulk as an additional driver?
You really need a girlfriend.
(GASPING) Mailman's here!
Aw. Remember when he used to
get that excited to see us?
Do you have any mail
for Doctor Sheldon Cooper?
I do, but I can't hand it right to you,
I have to put it in the box.
And that is what
separates the U.S. Postal Service
from those hippies at FedEx.
Oh, goody.
What is so exciting?
It's a letter from Doctor Wolcott.
We've been corresponding
about my string theory research.
Wait, Robert Wolcott?
Like Wolcott's Theorem, Wolcott?
The very same.
RAJ: Didn't he go crazy
and cut off all contact with people?
HOWARD: Yeah, he was driven mad
by a friend
who kept wanting to
talk about the Hulk's car insurance.
Oh, he's invited me
to his cabin for the weekend
To discuss a breakthrough he's had.
HOWARD: His cabin?
Yes, he lives off the grid
up in the mountains.
So, you're gonna
go to the middle of nowhere
and spend the weekend
with a crazy man you've never met?
Yes, why?
No reason, have fun.
(THEME SONG PLAYING)
SHELDON: Hmm.
Oh.
Hmm.
(LAUGHING) Nice one.
Hey, Penny, that's what you sound like
when you read.
- Hey.
- What, he said it.
Sheldon, what are you doing?
I'm decoding Doctor Wolcott's letter
using this book as the key.
Aren't conversations more fun
when they're in code?
Yes, but I'm using a code
where "yes" means "no."
Oh, I got it.
He's given me directions to his cabin.
Seems a little paranoid.
Wha- He is not paranoid.
(CLEARING THROAT)
What are you doing?
Following his instructions.
Leonard, you are not letting
Sheldon go alone this weekend.
Well, I am a grown man,
I don't need somebody to chaperone me.
I just need him to drop me off,
pick me up and pack me a sack lunch.
Don't look at me.
When the music stopped,
you were holding Sheldon.
Amy can't take him, it's her
bachelorette party this weekend.
Yes, it is! Because I'm getting married!
Are you gonna be doing that all weekend?
Yes, do you know why?
Because you're getting married!
(WHOOPING)
All right, Leonard,
looks like you're driving me.
But maybe you could drop me
at the bottom of the mountain,
I want him to think I'm cool.
HOWARD: That's great,
everyone's got weekend plans.
Amy has her bachelorette party
and Sheldon's gonna go to the woods
and get hunted for sport.
Yeah, as someone who has to track him
every time he gets lost in IKEA,
I fee I like I'd be really good at that.
Leonard, you cannot drop him off,
you have to stay with him
and keep him safe.
Howard, you have to go
and keep Leonard safe.
- Fine.
-l get it.
And you want me to go
and keep Howard safe.
- Actually, I-
- Just say yes
or he's gonna want to
come to the bachelorette party.
Are you sure
you're going to be okay this weekend?
Of course.
I'm much more concerned about you.
I know how you gals behave
when the men are away.
You do?
I've read the Bacchae by Euripides.
Drinking wine, riding panthers...
Proof that girls have gone wild
for over 2500 years.
Well, I wish I could say
none of that is gonna happen,
but Penny is planning it,
and she is the reason I own those
underwear with writing across the butt.
Well, just be careful
and use protection.
What do you think is gonna happen?
I don't know, but it's going to be sunny
and you burn easily.
It'll be fine.
I'm sure there'll be some drinking
and some dancing
and then a mailman will probably show up
and take his clothes off.
Nicholas is going to
take his clothes off?
No, not our mailman.
A dancer pretending to be a mailman.
Impersonating a federal employee,
oh, where's the after party, prison?
It's sweet that you're worried about me.
Well, of course I'm worried about you.
I want you to be safe.
And I want you to be safe.
I will be. I'll have my friends with me.
If anything should go wrong
I can use them as human shields.
LECTURER ON RECORDING:
For most of human history,
time was believed to be
an objective part of reality.
But with the contributions
of immanuel Kant,
science and philosophy charted-
When I said you should make a playlist
for the road trip, I meant music.
This is better than music.
This is a lecture on non-linear time.
Sounds like it's just on regular time.
Yes, but I put it on shuffle.
This is nice.
The four of us
haven't taken a trip like this
since Leonard's bachelor party.
And now here we are for Sheldon's.
(STAMMERING) Leonard...
As Sheldon's best man,
I need to inform you
that this is not a bachelor party.
And tell them why.
Because you're a tiresome scold.
No. It's because a bachelor party is
typically a hedonistic blow-out
where no pleasures
of the flesh are denied.
I'm not interested in that.
How is that not exactly what I said?
Okay, now, I promised Sheldon things
weren't gonna get too crazy tonight.
Should I be worried?
Just about who you're marrying.
(CLEARING THROAT)
Just come on.
Welcome to your bachelorette party!
(GASPING)
(UNSURELY) Oh.
It's a quilting bee!
My bachelorette party's a quilting bee!
(LAUGHING UNSURELY)
Isn't it perfect?
Yeah, instead of oiled-up strippers
and sex toys we thought,
"What does Amy like?"
Amy likes a quilting bee.
RAJ: Well, this place is creepy.
SHELDON: Why?
Did you see his vegetable garden?
Heirloom tomatoes in April.
creepy-
Okay, listen. Doctor Wolcott
is a brilliant topologist,
we need to set some ground rules
so that you don't embarrass me.
No magic. No whining. You, just no.
Hey...
How come he gets to whine?
Doctor Wolcott. Doctor Wolcott.
Doctor Wolcott.
(LOCKS UNLOCKING)
(MORE LOCKS UNLOCKING)
That's a lot of locks.
That's a lot of knocks.
They're made for each other.
Doctor Wolcott.
Doctor Cooper. Uh, who are these people?
Oh, these are my friends.
I wrote about them in my letter.
Oh, letter? I didn't get a letter.
Oh, that's because
ljust sent it this morning,
so score one for linear time.
Well, um, I don't normally
allow strangers into my house.
But when you do,
you let them out, right?
Doctor Cooper, if you can promise me
these men share
your intellect and academic rigor,
yeah, I suppose they can join us.
You guys might need to wait in the car.
Well, let me show you around.
This is the chair
where I do most of my thinking.
My thinking about work.
Now, my thinking about people
who have wronged me, I do over there.
I've always said that
I should get a grudge chair.
Leonard, have I not always said that?
You have, but you were worried
you'd spend too much time in it.
Well... That is a real concern.
Oh, my God, this tomato is amazing!
I can eat it like an apple.
My secret is I fertilize it
with my own manure.
The look on your face. (GIGGLING)
It's a sort of grin,
you wanna know what kind?
So, Doctor Wolcott,
in your letter you said you had
a new mathematical approach
that would help me conceptualize
the dimensions in string theory.
Ah, yes, yes, yes, yes.
But, before we get started,
lam going to need
to collect everybody's phones.
- Oh.
- LEONARD: Why?
Because they are
little listening devices, aren't they?
Yes, for people to spy on you
and steal your work.
Yeah, what happened to the good old days
where if someone
wanted to steal your work
they had to hire a prostitute
to seduce you?
Who told you about that?
Just making a joke.
Yeah, it's not funny when it happens.
All right, now, you're probably going to
want to start with this notebook here.
- Oh.
- Here we are.
Oh, my. on. (CHUCKLING)
Um, no offense, Doctor Wolcott,
but I'm not sure this makes any sense.
That's because
I've written it all backwards.
You- Wow.
That's "wow" backwards.
You... Um, I still don't get it.
Well, plus, the numbers are letters
and letters are numbers.
(INHALING) Oh.
I love him.
Are you having fun?
Yeah, ljust, uh,
finished sewing this top-to-bottom,
and now
I'm going to sew it side-to-side.
- Pace yourself.
-(BOTH CHUCKLING)
- Some more tea?
- Oh, lovely.
Oh!
Seriously? What the hell?
- Huh?
- What?
This is my bachelorette party,
tea and quilts?
Well, you said
you didn't want anything crazy.
Yes, but I said it like,
"I don't want anything crazy,"
which clearly means
I wanted something crazy.
I mean,
is this how boring you think I am?
Penny, she asked you a question.
Of course not.
So, you thought that
I would like quilting?
Well, don't you?
Of course, I like quilting,
it's the slowest way to make a blanket.
But this is my bachelorette party.
It's supposed to be fun and wild
and full of bad decisions.
Hey, we can make bad decisions.
Yeah, she had two kids back-to-back
and I thought you'd like this,
so we're off to a good start.
Come on, let's go somewhere we can do
body shots off shirtless bartenders.
Yes.
Oh, I don't know,
that might be too much.
All right, you know what, why don't
we stay home and have a little wine-
What are you not getting about this?
Doctor Wolcott,
your work on time is revolutionary.
I would say thank you,
but in my theory of time
you've already
called my work revolutionary,
I've already thanked you,
and I hate repeating myself,
so let's move on.
Wait a minute. Are you saying
that time has multiple dimensions,
the same as space?
No, no. I'm not saying it,
the math is saying it.
Though, it is the math that I invented,
so, yes, I guess I am saying it.
You understanding any of this?
I haven't understood anything
since poop-tomato.
My goodness, this is incredible.
See, I... I'm just not seeing
where string theory fits into all this
and that's where I think that you and I
could be of help to each other.
Thank you, I'd be honored.
All right. Allow me to
show you my most recent journal.
Sheldon's right,
this guy... This guy's brilliant.
Yeah, I mean, he's a little kooky,
but a mind that can reconceptualize time
probably has a reason
for keeping a jar of toenail clippings
that we just don't understand.
I could spend months up here
just going through his math.
You know, I think Sheldon might.
Great, who's gonna tell Amy
we lost her fiancé
to a mad man in the mountains?
Hey, I drove.
This is so exciting.
Can we do a body shot?
I've always wanted to do a body shot.
Also, what's a body shot?
It's when you take a drink
out of a stranger's belly button.
Oh, no thanks.
What if they have an outie?
Does it just spill everywhere?
Okay, look, we've got all night.
Let's just take it easy-
I'm getting married!
(CHEERING)
Here you go, first round's on the house.
- Ooh.
- Hey, there. Do you do body shots?
Oh. She said she didn't want one-
Mind your business.
Cheers! (WHOOPING)
Amy? Amy? Should we get her home?
Why? She's sound asleep
and we have sliders coming.
One more round.
So, how would this work
in the context of a singularity?
Yes, that's a tricky bit to explain.
I assume you're familiar
with non-abelian group theory.
Oh, and how! You never
forget your first group theory.
Listen, I'm going to put
on a pot of coffee,
because there's a
lot of math to go through.
And he said he didn't
want a wild bachelor party.
Excuse me?
Oh, Sheldon is getting married
in a month.
Oh, congratulations.
Yeah, I'm a married man myself.
Oh, really? ls she here?
And alive?
And... And can people
other than you see her?
She lives in Munich.
It's a perfect marriage.
We focus on our work and send each other
cards every year on our birthdays.
Wait, what... What month is it?
- Uh, April.
- Most years.
The point is we give each other space.
I give her Europe,
she gives me South America,
that's where she thinks I'm living.
Oh, I... I've never considered
a long distance marriage.
Well, listen,
if you want to be a great scientist
you can't afford to be distracted.
Hey, where are my manners?
You fellows must be hungry.
- Do you like rabbit?
- Yeah. Sure.
- Sounds good.
- Okay.
But can you tell the
difference between rabbit and squirrel?
- No. Don't think so.
- Probably not.
Great, we're having rabbit.
Be right back.
It's amazing how much he's accomplished
by isolating himself from
the distractions of day-to-day life.
Okay, please don't tell me
you wanna live like this.
See, that's the strange thing, I don't.
What is wrong with me?
Why don't I want this?
Look how cool it all is.
Nothing is wrong with you.
You have friends, you have a fiancée.
You have a full life.
You know what? You're right.
Thank you for bringing me up here.
But I think I'm ready to go home now.
Really? You don't want to stay
for dinner and talk more science?
No, no, we better go. I miss Amy.
And my phone.
(GUN FIRING)
Also, I'm from Texas
and I can taste the difference
between rabbit and squirrel.
(TV PLAYING MUSIC)
Whoa... Huh?
- Oh, look who's back.
- There she is.
What happened? How did we get here?
You don't remember anything?
I remember taking some shots
and then... That's it.
Oh, my gosh, did I pass out?
You kinda did.
At my own bachelorette party?
I'm so lame.
Oh, you didn't pass out
before you did all kinds of fun stuff.
What did I do?
(INCREDULOUSLY) What did you do?
(IN NORMAL VOICE) What did she do?
Um, well, you don't remember
Riverdancing on top of the bar?
- I did that?
- Yeah, you did.
Mmm.
But I don't know how to Riverdance.
Didn't stop you from
teaching all those shirtless firemen.
I saw shirtless firemen?
Saw, smelled, slid down like a pole.
Did I flash anybody?
How about "everybody"?
I can't believe it, I'm so embarrassed.
You didn't take any pictures, did you?
Oh, no, we would never do that to you.
Yeah, but if there were pictures,
they would be (SINGSONG) crazy.
- You guys are good friends.
- PENNY: Mmm.
(IRISH FIDDLE MUSIC PLAYING)
Dinner!
Guys?
I can't believe they left
without saying goodbye.
Wait a minute,
what if they stole my work?
what if they were never here at all?
Wait a minute,
what if they haven't gotten here yet
but they're on their way?
I'd better tidy up.
Hello.
Welcome back. How did it go?
Doctor Wolcott's theories of time
might save
my new interpretation of string theory.
Well, that's exciting.
Yeah, it is.
How was your bachelorette party?
Well, I was in a bar
and I saw some shirtless men.
They were firemen
and they fought over me.
But, Penny and Bernadette
got me out of there
before the victor got my spoils.
I see.
What's the matter? You look glum.
Amy, would you still love me
if I wasn't who you thought I was?
What are you talking about?
Well, what if it turns out
I'm not the single-minded,
science-obsessed recluse
who puts his work
above everything and everybody else
that you fell in love with?
What if I'm not the straight-laced,
buttoned-up,
quilting queen you thought I was?
What if I'm a Riverdancing wild woman?
I'd still love you.
I'd still love you, too.
Do you really know how to Riverdance?
You tell me.
I'm the only man you do that for.
(THEME SONG PLAYING)