Why are you wearing a Band-Aid?
Halley bit me.
(LAUGHS) You got beaten up by a girl.
Hey, that's sexist.
You're right.
(LAUGHS) You got beaten up by a baby.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Whatcha got there?
I grabbed a sandwich
from the food truck out front.
(STAMMERS) Hold on, tonight is Friday
and I believe you know what that means.
That my fun, young life
took a drastic turn somewhere.
- No.
- But, yeah.
No, that means it's Chinese food night.
Yeah, and you have Chinese food,
so eat it.
But, I can smell your pastrami.
And we can all hear your complaining,
so, no one's happy.
It does smell good.
It is, I had one the other day.
What is happening?
Everybody's supposed to be
eating Chinese food.
Well, actually, I believe the Chinese
may have invented the sandwich.
Their dish "rou jia mo" literally means
"meat between bread."
So, looks like all of us, including
Penny, are eating Chinese food.
Except for you Sheldon,
you're eating crow.
I'm sorry, I think you're forgetting
that the sandwich
was invented by John Montagu,
the Earl of Sandwich.
Oh! The truck's called
Pearl of Sandwich. Now, I get it. Mmm.
All right, that smells too good.
I gotta get one of those.
And, I think you're forgetting that
there are written documents
of meat between bread being eaten
in China during the Tang Dynasty.
You know what, I'll go with you.
And then, maybe we just go home.
I think you're defining bread
very loosely.
If we go down that road,
where does it end?
I would say when we go to bed,
but you talk in your sleep.
I don't want to get into this
with you right now.
We'll talk about this when I'm asleep.
I don't wanna talk about it
when you're asleep.
How come we can't talk about it now?
Because I'm eating now.
Fine, how's your Moo shu?
You know what, it's great.
What? Look at that.
Hmm.
Maybe the Chinese did invent
the sandwich.
I guess you were right.
Too bad no one's around to hear it.
(THEME SONG PLAYING)
I can smell that food truck
from up here.
Just close the window
if you don't like the smell.
Of course, I like the smell,
it's salt and fat.
My brain may be evolved
but my tongue still wants to
pick up a club
and drag that truck back to my cave.
So there's something you like
but it's also driving you crazy.
Been there, doing it now.
No, it's a distraction.
Now, how can I focus on my work
when all I can think about
is how much I want that sandwich?
So, go get one.
I can't just give into every urge
I have when I have it.
That's why I have a rigid schedule.
It's bad enough I had to give into
my urge to create a rigid schedule.
You know, why don't ljust go down
to the food truck and ask them to move?
- Why are you taking cash?
- No reason.
Ah! This is the life.
What could be better than this?
If you weren't wearing
one of my swimsuits.
I'll give it back.
Huh. You know the rule.
Once it touches heinie,
it's no longer miney.
You're such a prude. Do you know all the
things this water is touching right now?
Well, I'm relaxed enough.
Hey, Howard, look.
What's that?
HOWARD: Huh.
Looks like someone's drone.
Oh, no, do you it was spying on us
in the hot tub?
'Cause I'm only 40% of the way
to my beach-bod.
One of the propellers is broken,
it must've crashed.
Oh. Do you think you could fix it?
Maybe. Should we try
and track down the owner first?
Yeah. That's probably a good idea.
Anyone lose a drone?
Looks like it's ours.
Yay, we got a drone!
- Shh!
-(WHISPERS) Oh! Yay, we got a drone.
The pastrami truck moved.
That is the danger
of a restaurant on wheels.
No, apparently someone complained
to the tenants association.
They're not allowed to park
on our street anymore.
Who would complain about something
that everyone loves? Oh.
Did you complain to the tenants
association about the food truck?
- Yes.
- PENNY: Wha...
They actually took you seriously?
(SIGHS)
Oh, the tenants association
takes every complaint seriously.
Great, because I'm about to send them
an email complaining about you.
-(PENNY SIGHS)
-(CELL PHONE CHIMES)
Excuse me.
Wow.
Someone should have spell-checked.
- What is going on here?
- You're the tenants association?
(LAUGHS) You should see
the look on your face.
And you might want to tell your wife
that there's no "Y" in pastrami.
Okay, that oughta do it,
I've replaced the propeller and
reattached the gimbal controller unit.
Dude, you're like
Grey's Anatomy for robots.
Also, why isn't that a show?
I just need to see if I can re-sync
the controls to this old remote.
We should name it.
What? The drone
or your stupid robot show?
The drone. The show's already
got a name, General Bot-spital.
(WHIRRING)
I got it working! (CHUCKLES)
RAJESH: Oh! Oh!
Let's play William Tell.
I'll put this bowl on my head,
see if you can knock it off
without hitting me.
You read my mind.
What are you doing?
Either breaking a bowl
or breaking Raj's head.
Be careful, they don't make
that bowl anymore.
It's a nice one.
Yeah, we found it in the yard
and fixed it up.
Aren't you worried there's some kid
out there missing his drone?
Oh, please, Bernadette,
this is not a children's toy, okay?
This thing's got a HD camera on it.
Okay, then aren't you worried
there's some rich Peeping Tom
out there missing his drone?
We asked around and no one claimed it.
Ha. I think we've done all we can do.
Did you check the video card?
Maybe you could see
where it started off from.
(WHISPERS) What a great idea, honey.
So, let me get this straight,
you are the president
of the tenants association?
President, only member
and harshest critic.
I once gave myself an official reprimand
for conducting a meeting in the shower.
The steam warped my gavel.
Okay, so, when I got a fine for leaving
my clothes in the dryer too long,
that was from you?
$14.99, the exact price of a new gavel.
And the noise complaint we got
for singing you "Happy Birthday?"
As a friend, I was touched.
As a representative of the building,
I thought that you should pick a key
and stick with it.
Hi.
Do you know he's
the entire tenants association?
No, but I'm not surprised.
He's also the pope of a planet
he invented in hyperspace.
Why didn't you tell me?
I wanted to make that sure
you loved the man, not the office.
You can't just
declare yourself president.
I didn't. I called a meeting,
I was the only one to attend,
I nominated myself
and after a pretty moving speech,
I voted myself in.
Well, if you can vote yourself in,
then we can vote you out.
- Yeah.
- Fine make a motion at the next meeting.
When is that?
It's the first Saturday
of every month.
Unless there's an emergency meeting.
Then we call an emergency meeting.
You don't really have to,
this is the first Saturday of the month.
Okay, fine, then, we vote you out.
(STAMMERS) Hold 0n, hold on,
first, we have to read the minutes
from last month's meeting.
Amy, would you do the honors?
Why not?
"Saturday, March third,
7:05, meeting called to order.
"7:06, president gets shampoo in eye."
SHELDON: Mmm-hmm.
"7:07, meeting adjourned."
Okay, can we vote you out now?
Ah! Very well. New business.
I move for a vote of no confidence
in the president.
- Yeah.
- Two to one, you lose.
Not so fast.
I believe we have one tenant here
who has not made her voice heard.
Oh.
We're waiting, fiancée.
Yeah, we're waiting, best friend.
Yeah, we're waiting,
neighbor who needed a battery
and totally got one from me,
no strings attached.
I don't wanna be in the middle of this.
No matter which way I vote,
I'm either a bad friend,
a bad fiancée or
an ungrateful recipient of a battery.
Next time I have a meeting
in the shower, you're welcome to attend.
Sheldon, Sheldon for president,
I pick Sheldon.
Can't believe my best friend
sided with Sheldon.
Can't believe my best friend is Sheldon.
Ugh. I should've taken that gavel
and shoved it right down his throat.
Ugh. I would've gone the other way
but it would've gotten to this throat.
What?
Don't be mad at me,
I mean, I can't vote against him.
What? Even when he's being crazy?
What other times are there?
So you'll just let him
get away with anything?
Well, not anything,
but honestly, pastrami sandwich
is not the hill I want to die on.
It's not about the sandwich,
it's about the principle.
Yeah, principle.
And a little bit sandwich.
Yeah.
Look, there are a bunch of other
tenants in this building,
all you need is
for one of them to vote your way,
and then Sheldon's out
and I didn't betray him.
Hey, you know
that's actually a good plan.
That you came up with all by yourself.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
told Sheldon I was going to the market
so taking some of your stuff.
I was never here.
Sometimes you don't see it
'cause she's next to Sheldon,
but she's pretty weird.
Okay, all hooked up. Here we go.
(SIGHS) I hope there's
nothing disturbing on there.
Like you two in a hot tub?
Hold on, now I'm getting a picture.
It's not very much to go on.
Oh, that's plenty to go on.
We can't give up, we gotta find her.
You just wanna find her
'cause she's cute.
Not just because she's cute.
She also owns a pretty expensive drone
which means she has money
and doesn't mind wasting it
and I... I like that in a woman.
Do you see anything
that can help us locate her?
Mmm, let me have a look.
She's got eagle eyes.
Always spotting
continuity errors in movies.
(CHUCKLES) It's not annoying at all.
Oh, there. Right there.
Check out the pin on her jacket,
isn't that from the comic book store?
Mmm. ls it? Hey, Howard, zoom in.
Fine, zooming in.
(VOCALIZES WHOOSHING)
Yeah, I know you're being a jerk,
but it's actually helpful.
Hey.
Hi, we're your neighbors
from downstairs.
We've met.
Remember I invited you
to my housewarming when I moved in?
Oh, yeah, sorry, you know,
it's been a crazy couple of months.
That was two years ago.
Welcome to the building.
So I'm running for
president of the tenants association,
I could really use your vote.
You said you were gonna stop by,
I bought a lot of food.
Anyway, meeting's tomorrow,
we really hope you can make it.
- I'll be there.
- Ah, really?
Yeah, you should buy a lot of food.
So, I'm running for
president of the tenants association
and I could really use your vote.
Uh, who's president now?
Uh, Sheldon Cooper.
You know, about yay tall
and about yay annoying.
(CHUCKLES)
So you want me to vote
against Sheldon Cooper?
Yeah. You just need to show up
at a meeting and-
Oh, no, no, no can do.
He's got a restraining order against me.
Really? Why?
I locked him on the roof once.
(LAUGHS, WHISPERS) Three times.
So, Mrs. Petrescu, we were hoping
you would vote for Leonard
instead of voting for Sheldon.
Vote Sheldon.
No, no, vote Leonard.
No, vote Leonard.
No. Vote Leonard.
Thank you.
She's wearing a pin from your store.
Do you know who she is?
Oh, sure, yeah, that's Cynthia.
Wha... So she's a customer?
Yeah, yeah,
but I... I haven't seen her in a while.
And before you say anything,
there's a lot of reasons
women stop coming here,
it's not just me.
But this time?
It was me. Yeah.
I was trying out a flirty new smile.
Now, I don't use
the word "ghoulish" a lot
(SIGHS) but ljust can't think
of another word.
Wait, do you know how to find her?
Yeah, I think I have her address
on my mailing list.
Hey, please let me bring
the drone back to her.
You think you've got a shot?
What if she's married?
- She's not.
-It's meant to be.
Little tip. Uh,
stick with the smiles you know.
Hi, what are you doing?
Leonard and Penny are trying to turn
the tenants against me.
So they are about to see
just what kind of power
the president
of the tenants association wields.
"You must be at least this tall
to use washing machine."
I'm going to hang it up higher
than Leonard.
Then his clothes will smell
and nobody's voting for a man
with smelly clothes. No.
Not when there's a perfectly
unscented incumbent on the ballot.
Sheldon, I have an advanced degree
in the study of the human brain,
so if my fiancé's a raving lunatic,
it's kind of a ding on my reputation.
If leaders just stepped aside every time
they didn't have the consent
of the governed, what would we have?
Democracy.
Not on my watch.
Okay, don't be weird,
don't be weird, don't be weird.
(IN DEEP VOICE) Hello.
Hey, you found my drone.
Yeah, yes, it took a while
to track you down,
but to see the look on your face,
it was worth it.
Aw.
That's sweet. (CHUCKLES)
Rajesh.
- Cynthia.
- Pleasure to meet you.
Likewise.
I feel like I should give you
a reward or something.
Oh, no, you don't have to do that.
- No, I insist.
- How about your phone number?
Give me your phone.
Thanks. So, I'll call you, Cynthia.
- Great, Rajesh.
-(BOTH CHUCKLE)
- And thanks again.
- Uh, sure.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
RAJESH: Just checking.
(KNOCKS ON DOOR)
Hey, Sheldon,
we found something pretty interesting.
Huh.
Well, that is surprising.
I for one have no idea
what they're talking about.
Turns out, when Amy took over
Penny's apartment
she was put on the lease, not you.
Yeah and when I moved across the hall
you got taken off the lease
and I got added.
What are you saying?
That Sheldon's not technically
a tenant at all
and therefore has no standing to be
president of the tenants association
no matter who votes for him?
I don't know how you found that out
but I'm guessing all on your own.
So looks like we need to figure out
who the new president should be.
- I nominate myself.
- I second it.
Huh.
Well, as a woman in love,
I want to stand by my man.
Too bad that's been rendered
bureaucratically impossible.
Well, this is hard for me
because I do love a legal technicality,
and this is a good one.
Although not quite as good
as the provision in California law
which states a person who occupies
a dwelling for thirty consecutive days
becomes a tenant at will. And as such-
- I vote for Leonard.
- You...
What?
I'm sorry, Sheldon.
With minimal power
comes minimal responsibility,
and you couldn't handle it.
You-
Don't you misquote Spider-Man to me.
It's not your fault.
I mean, what man
wouldn't be seduced by the power
To decide how late
the laundry room stays open?
Wait, you're the reason I had to come
back and get my jeans the next morning?
I can't believe you expect me
to give that up.
(PENNY SIGHS)
Sheldon, it's the American way,
the peaceful transfer of power.
I don't know.
Think about Ant-Man.
I'm always thinking about Ant-Man.
Michael Douglas had the suit
and then he passed it on to Paul Rudd.
(SIGHS)
Maybe you're right.
Really? The Ant-Man thing,
that's what won you over?
Yes, he got the details right,
that's how you use a superhero.
(BOTH SIGH)
I suppose it is time
I pass this on to Leonard.
- Thank you.
- Yeah, thanks.
Uh, I know that's hard for you.
Well, it was, but you know what?
Instead of being in charge,
I can now be the vocal opposition,
criticizing and badgering
the president at every turn.
I think you'll be really good at that.
Me too.
I think I've made a huge mistake.
Can't believe you got her number.
(SIGHS) I know, right?
How amazing would it be
if this worked out
and the story of howl met my wife
started with you and me
in the hot tub together?
(CHUCKLES)
No, do us both a favor
and start the story later.
Whatever. I have a good feeling about
this girl, like we really hit it off.
RAJESH". Stop flying it around,
you're gonna break it.
-(DRONE BUZZING)
- Why do you care?
Because we have to give it back
to the beautiful mystery girl.
- Aw.
-l mean, did you see how hot she was!
I want to get all up on that
and start making babies.
I know exactly what underwear
I'm gonna wear on our first date.
None!
(THEME SONG PLAYING)
English - SDH