LEONARD: Previously on
The Big Bang Theory...
I was offered a summer research
fellowship at Princeton.
A fine institution.
The place where Albert Einstein taught.
And where Leonard got his PhD,
so it may have gone downhill.
Gentlemen, you may remember
Dr. Nowitzki,
she's back at Caltech for her post-doc.
- RAMONA: Hello. (CHUCKLES)
- ALL: Hi.
Question,
are you seeking
a romantic relationship with me?
What if I were?
Well, that would raise
a number of problems.
We're colleagues,
I'm currently in a--
SHELDON: Amy. (KNOCKING AT DOOR)
Amy. Amy.
Will you marry me?
(SHELDON'S CELL PHONE RINGING)
One moment please.
Really, you're gonna
answer that right now?
It's Leonard, I don't want to be rude.
- Hello?
- Hey, where you been?
We've been calling you for hours.
I'm sorry,
my phone was on airplane mode.
Why?
Because I was on an airplane.
(MOUTHING)
Hey, put him on speaker.
- Yeah.
- Hey. Where are you?
SHELDON: I came to Princeton to see Amy.
(CHUCKLES) It's a funny story actually.
I was having lunch with Dr. Nowitzki
-and she kissed me.
- Excuse me?
Rm sorry?
Wait, and in that moment I realized that
Amy was the only woman
I ever wanted to kiss
for the rest of my life.
So, I came to New Jersey
to ask her to marry me.
- Oh, that's so sweet.
-(CHUCKLES)
Sheldon.
Yeah, although there was one man
whose blessing I needed first.
I've thought about it
and I really wanna spend
the rest of my life with Amy.
Do I have your blessing?
Well, Sheldon,
I think you should make
her finger like Saturn
and put a ring on it.
You asked Stephen Hawking
and not her father?
Stephen Hawking's a genius.
If he said no, I wasn't gonna waste
my time on her father.
But you did ask my father?
- Mm-hmm, I did, he said, "Yes."
-(GASPS)
Although not in a robot voice
so it wasn't nearly as cool.
Okay, oh, my God, I can't believe
you guys are engaged!
SHELDON: We're not engaged yet,
she's taking forever to answer.
Because you're on the phone!
We'll call you back.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
SHELDON: She said, "Yes."
- Yay! (SCREAMS)
- Congratulations!
(THEME SONG PLAYING)
Mother, I have some good news to share.
We're engaged! (CHUCKLES)
I am so happy for you two.
But I'm not surprised.
I've been praying for this.
Well, God had nothing to do with it.
It happened because
I was kissing another woman
and it made me realize
I wanted to be with Amy.
More than one woman
was interested in you?
I might have prayed a little too hard.
(STUTTERS) I just-- I wanna
let you know right now
that we are not getting married
in a church.
That's all right, Sheldon,
anywhere Jesus is is a church.
Well, he won't be at our wedding.
He's in my heart,
so if I'm there he'll be there.
Okay, well, then he's your plus one,
you don't get to bring anyone else.
That's fine, love you.
All right, love you too, bye.
Lord, thank you.
(SIGHS) Even though you can do anything,
that was mighty impressive.
We're engaged.
Oh, my God, that's amazing!
(STUTTERS) Wait, tell me everything.
Well, Dr. Nowitzki was kissing me--
Oh, you can stop leading
with that part of the story.
Well, congratulations,
I'm so happy for you two.
Hold on, I have to tell Bernadette.
Hey, Bernie, guess what,
Sheldon and Amy got engaged!
Can you believe it?
Oh, my God.
I cannot believe it.
She's so happy,
I think she's crying. (LAUGHS)
Do you think Sheldon's gonna want
some weird Star Trek wedding?
I don't know.
Well, Leonard could barely finish
the words "Doctor Who wedding cake"
before I shut that down hard.
Mm-hmm.
Are you listening to me?
Yeah, you're mean to Leonard,
I heard you.
Is everything okay?
(SIGHS SOFTLY) Look, I'm gonna
tell you something,
but you can't freak out,
because I'm already freaking out.
Oh, my God, what is it?
(SIGHS) I'm pregnant again.
Wha--
Interesting.
Howard's gonna lose his mind.
Wait, you haven't told him yet?
- No.
- So you told me first?
Oh, Bernie.
This wasn't supposed to happen.
We were careful.
I didn't even think you could get
pregnant while you were breastfeeding.
Well, guess what, you can.
Hey, look, this is a good thing.
Hailey's gonna have
a little brother or sister to play with.
I guess that would be pretty cute.
And, you know,
I was a surprise to my parents,
and my dad said it was the best thing
that ever happened to them.
Okay, maybe this baby
actually is a blessing.
Oh, my God, honey, of course it is.
(CHUCKLES)
- How am I pregnant again?
- Yeah, what were you thinking?
All right.
I'm all checked into my flight.
Well I'm sad you're leaving,
Why'd you only book a flight
for one day?
I came here to propose.
If you'd said "No;-
I wouldn't want to stick around
looking at your stupid face.
Now, mind you, your face is only stupid
in the "no" version of the story.
But I said, "Yes,"
so I get a lifetime of this.
Yes, you do, smart face.
Why don't you stay a few extra days?
Well, I don't have any other clothes.
We'll get you some.
I don't know, I'm pretty particular.
Well, there's a comic book store
less than a mile from here.
Perfect, let's go shopping.
Oh, um, and I'm having dinner
with some colleagues tonight,
I'm sure they'd love to meet you.
- Aw.
- Come on. What do you say?
Aw, you're nagging me.
It's like we're already married.
- Is that a "yes" or a "no"?
- Geez, save some for the honeymoon.
Look at Nowitzki over there.
Can't believe she tried to steal
Sheldon from Amy.
You know what? I'm gonna go there
and tell her that they're engaged now
and that her little plan didn't work.
Because you're sticking up for Sheldon,
or because you're still mad
she rejected you?
Too far away, can't hear you.
- Hello, Ramona.
- Hello.
Why are you sitting by yourself?
Oh, that's right, Sheldon's
in New Jersey, being engaged to Amy.
I heard.
Now that Sheldon's out of the picture,
I could give you one more chance
to go out with me.
Nope, I'm good.
You sure?
I will not ask again.
I sincerely hope not.
Very well. I'm going to leave
before this gets awkward.
Hey. Want me to make dinner?
All right. Sure, but first,
why don't you have a seat.
There is something I need to show you.
Ooh, if it's "How to make dinner"
that'd be great. (LAUGHS)
(SIGHS)
Is this a...
pregnancy test?
Yes.
That means...
positive?
Yes.
No.
- Yes.
- Oh, no, no. (LAUGHS)
Yes.
No.
How could this even happen?
(STUTTERS) I mean, we were careful.
Well, it did.
- No! No!
- Yes! Yes!
- No! No! No!
- Yes! Yes! Yes!
Okay, okay, okay, (GASPS) well, wh--
what are-- what are we gonna do?
What do you mean,
"What are we gonna do?"
We're gonna have another baby.
- No.
- Stop that!
- No! I'm trying!
- Yes.
(SIGHS) Look, I know it's scary,
but we're both responsible adults,
we can do this.
(SIGHS) You really think so? (SIGHS)
Yeah.
No!
Hey, Stuart.
Oh, hey, Raj, what can I help you with?
I need to buy an engagement gift.
Well, you came to the wrong place.
(CHUCKLES) It's for Sheldon and Amy.
No way, they're engaged?
- Yeah.
- Ah, that's exciting news.
Who would've thought Sheldon and Amy
would be the next two to tie the knot.
Tell me about it.
I'm the one who caught the bouquet
at Leonard and Penny's wedding.
Okay, uh, you know,
they might like this,
Superman and Wonder Woman.
It's kinda romantic.
Mm.
You know what,
why am I buying them a gift?
They have love,
screw them and their happiness.
What do you have for someone
who's bitter and alone?
Literally, everything.
Sheldon, these are the heads
of my research team.
- Hello.
- Dr. Zane, Dr. Harris,
this is my fiancé,
Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
That's the first time I've said that
and it kinda gave me the goosebumps.
Dr. Cooper, we are so excited
to meet you. (CHUCKLES)
Oh, well that's very kind of you.
If you'd like, I could
autograph your menus after dinner. Yeah.
But I better not see those on eBay.
(DR. ZANE LAUGHS)
No, no, no. We're, we're just excited
to meet the man
who landed this brilliant woman here.
-(CHUCKLES)
- Oh, that wasn't hard,
she threw herself at me.
Now getting the universe
to show me its naughty bits,
that took some doing.
Sheldon's a physicist.
- Oh.
- That's nice.
Amy, I recently read your paper
on lesions in the olfactory receptors
in the brain.
(SIGHS) It was inspired.
(CHUCKLES)
Well, I guess it didn't stink.
But if it did, that rat wouldn't
have known it. (CHUCKLES)
(DR. ZANE LAUGHS)
(STUTTERS) I'm sorry, I'm sure
you don't wanna sit here
and listen to a bunch of work talk.
Oh, no, I love it. (STUTTERS)
Let's talk about work.
Amy's work, my work,
yeah, why don't we start with my work?
Actually, I do have a question
for Dr. Cooper.
When Amy first told you
about her approach to synaptic tracing,
did you think it was gonna
revolutionize the field?
(STUTTERS) Really,
that's your question?
What are you, Entertainment Tonight?
You know what? (STUTTERS)
I'm gonna give you a better question.
Here, "Dr. Cooper,
"I heard you were working on a top
secret project for the U.S. Military,
"why don't you tell us about that?"
See, that's a great question.
Okay, what was that like?
Well, I can't tell you that,
it's top secret.
Boy, that was exhausting.
And no offense, but your colleagues
were pretty rude.
- Really, they were rude?
- Yes,
they just kept talking about you
and how great you are
no matter how many times
I brought me up.
Well, these are my colleagues,
and they wanna talk about my work,
why does that bother you so much?
Because I was there.
It's like having Optimus Prime
over to dinner
and not asking him to turn into a truck.
You know what, Sheldon?
You're not always the smartest person
in every room.
You may not even be the smartest person
in this room.
Oh, I am sorry.
What, is Neil Degrasse Tyson
hiding behind the couch?
Because if he is, he's not that smart.
It's pretty dusty back there.
Hey, where are you going?
I'm storming off to my room.
Wait, then where am I supposed
to storm off to?
Well, you're so smart,
why don't you figure it out?
(DOOR CLOSES)
ls there another bedroom?
Perhaps (STUTTERS) a den?
So, how are you guys doin'
with all the new events in your womb?
Good, you know,
obviously it was a surprise.
There was some crying
and some yelling--
Some suggestion of make-up sex
that did not go over well even though
it's not like we can get more pregnant.
But then we realized
that it's a gift, in the sense that
we didn't ask for it,
and we may not have chosen it--
(CHEWING) And we already have one.
You know, whenever I find a top I like
I always go back and get a second one
in a different color.
Which I hope is not the case
with your baby.
Uh, uh, I know you guys are freaked out
but you're great parents
and if you ever need help
we are here for you.
Yeah. Anything at all, just ask.
Well, you know what you could do?
You could have a baby, too.
I'm sorry, what?
Well, that's a great idea.
We could go through it together,
wouldn't that be fun?
(SCOFFS)
You guys were just saying
how freaked out and miserable you are.
I say a lot of crazy things,
I'm pregnant and hormonal.
Do it, have a baby, do it!
Come on, it'd be so cute,
our kids playing together.
What do you say? Why don't you two hit
the old mattress and whip up a family?
Okay, we're not gonna have a baby
just to make you guys feel better.
Yeah, if we're gonna have a baby
it's gonna be when we are ready
or when I'm certain
Penny's gonna leave me.
Exactly.
They're my friends,
and I should be happy for them.
And I'm trying,
but, all I feel is this, like,
gnawing empty sensation in my gut.
- I had that once.
- Hmm.
Turned out it was a tapeworm.
Cool, uh...
It's just--
It's hard talking
to my other friends about this,
but I knew you would understand.
- Why is that?
- Because you and I are both alone,
which is actually kind of comforting
Because at least
we can be alone together.
(INHALES) Hmm, this is,
this is awkward. I, um,
I was actually gonna close up a little
early tonight 'cause I have a date.
- Really?
- Yeah.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Forgive me if I'm having trouble
being happy for you.
Don't be silly, I'm lovin' your pain.
Is this how our marriage is going to be?
Sometimes people will be more interested
in talking to her than to me?
Are you sitting in a bathroom?
(SIGHS) Yes,
I needed a place to storm off to
and it was all that was available.
Fine, but if I hear a flush
this conversation is over.
Those people were in the presence
of a world-class mind
and all they wanted to talk about
was their own nonsense.
Can you see the irony in that statement?
STEPHEN HAWKING: How about now?
HAWKING: How about now?
I'll wait.
Oh, surprise.
Oh, crap, is it our anniversary?
No. Wait.
- No.
- No. Okay.
All right, so what are we celebrating?
Well, Bernadette and Howard
are pregnant again,
Amy and Sheldon are getting married,
I didn't want you to feel left out.
Oh.
Left out?
Well, Bernadette has to grow
a baby inside of her
and Amy has to marry one.
My life is great!
(LAUGHS)
- So do you not want the cake--
- Try and take it away, see what happens.
Oh, crap, it is our anniversary.
Happy anniversary!
Amy...
There's something I need to say to you.
I'm listening.
(SIGHS)
I've been thinking about The Avengers.
I believe that,
but I don't think that's something
you needed to say to me.
(SIGHS)
I realized that Iron Man is great.
And also, that Captain America is great.
And sometimes Iron Man
is in a Captain America movie
and he's not mad
it's not an Iron Man movie.
Now he can fly in, give the audience
a thrill, and then fly away.
And that should have been me tonight.
I should have been
the delightful cameo in your movie.
Thank you, Sheldon.
Instead, I was like the Hulk and I--
Okay, please stop talking
about The Avengers.
Anyway,
I'm proud of you
and I'm going to try to do a betterjob
of sharing the spotlight
because we're a team,
you know, much like...
The Dodgers.
If they had superpowers.
And fought crime.
And Thor was in them.
Sheldon, I know this isn't easy,
but, you'll have a whole lifetime
to practice.
It could take that long,
I'm really bad at it.
You know, maybe, um...
I should start right now
and go back to Pasadena and let you have
this experience to yourself.
You just want to go back
'cause that's where everybody
makes a fuss over you.
You know, your colleagues are right,
you are brilliant.
Hello.
- Hey!
- Mm, hey, welcome back!
Oh, (STUTTERS) let me see the ring.
RAJESH: Ooh, nice.
Hey, hey, hey, hey,
her eyes are up there.
(CHUCKLES)
I-is that the woman who kissed Sheldon?
Uh.
- Could be.
- Hard to say.
Tell us about Princeton.
- Excuse me for a minute.
- Yeah. No, we'll catch up later.
This is going to be
the biggest smackdown
since my Aunt Noopur
showed up at the family reunion
wearing the same sari
as my cousin Shruti.
Dr. Nowitzki.
Oh. (CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Dr. Fowler,
hello.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
English - SDH