Hey, can you do me a favor?
Can we try to avoid talking to
our friends tonight
about our wedding plans?
I'll do you one better.
I'll avoid talking
to our friends entirely
and play on my phone.
It's just, I haven't picked
a maid of honor yet,
and I'm having trouble deciding
between Penny and Bernadette.
Ah. Understandable.
They are quite similar.
Both blonde former waitresses
who married beneath them.
Penny is my best friend,
but I was Bernadette's
maid of honor,
and I think
she kind of expects it.
So, if anyone brings
it up tonight,
just maybe you can help
me change the subject.
How about this?
I dominate the conversation so hard,
no one has a chance
to get a word in edgewise.
I don't know.
They might see that coming.
What if we have a code word?
Now you're speaking my catamaran.
That's my code word for "language."
Okay, fine, catamaran.
That's our code word.
No, that's my code word.
Get your own.
Okay. Pretzels.
You hear me say pretzels,
you change the subject.
Rhinos are my least favorite
animals at the zoo.
What?
Oh, I'm sorry. I thought we started.
Hey, just hold the gate
still while I screw it in.
You know, I don't know how I feel
about all this baby-proofing.
If Halley can't teach herself
to walk down the stairs,
then maybe that's nature's way
of saying
the Wolowitz line ends here.
That's funny.
I always thought
Howard was nature's way of saying
the Wolowitz line ends here.
Me, too, but life does
find a way!
Hey, Halley can't reach
the liquor cabinet.
Why did you baby-proof it?
How did you know we did?
Fair point.
- Bernadette still going stir-crazy?
- A little.
Two months of bed rest,
it's been rough.
Really? That sounds great.
How do I get that?
You'd either have to break your
hip or let Howard knock you up.
Now, either way, you'll get
flowers the next morning.
She's actually been
keeping herself busy
doing wedding research for you.
Oh! She doesn't have to do that.
She wants to. After all,
you were her maid of honor.
Sheldon, tell your funny story
about pretzels.
Oh. Right. Yeah, yeah.
Did you know that we've been thinking
of having pretzels
at our wedding?
No, no. I'm sorry.
No, rhinos. We're having
rhinos at our wedding.
No! I got to go.
I'm gonna need some help.
Someone baby-proofed the front door.
(THEME SONG PLAYING)
Sheldon, what am I gonna do
about my maid of honor?
I mean, Bernadette gave me
all these bridal magazines.
She even folded down the pages
with the good dresses.
I get it.
You know, Leonard
once borrowed
my Edmund Scientific catalog
and dog-eared some pages.
Never got 'em straight again.
Well, that is exactly the same thing.
You really understand my dilemma.
Actually, I do.
My mother
is pushing for my brother, Georgie,
to be my best man,
and I hate to disappoint her again.
I already rejected her savior
and her Linkedln invitation.
How are we gonna make these decisions
without anybody getting upset?
Well, what if we take emotion
out of the process,
and base it on empirical metrics?
Then we aren't really
making the decision,
the data is.
So we can hurt our friends' feelings
without taking any responsibility?
Me likey.
But how do we apply
quantitative metrics
to something as subjective
as choosing a wedding party?
That decision only seems subjective.
In reality,
people in a wedding party
perform very specific functions,
and some will perform those
better than others.
If I may use a superhero analogy-
- You may not.
- Okay, I'll use real people.
Um, if a certain dog-like loyalty
is useful,
then it's Leonard.
If having a PEZ dispenser
filled with TUMS is
an advantage, Wolowitz, yeah.
If a best man
with fake testicles hanging
from his truck is important,
well, then, my brother's
back in the running.
Okay, I see your point.
So, we break down
each of the roles
into their component parts,
and then design
specialized tests for each.
Exactly. Boy, if I had known
getting married was going to
involve so much science,
I'd have proposed years ago.
So Leonard, tell everyone your news.
I'm starting a book.
That would be big news from Penny,
but you've read a book before.
He means he's writing a book.
I do. It's something I've been
thinking about for a long time.
Yeah. It's about a brilliant physicist
who solves crimes using science.
- Oh, Leonard-
- It's not about you.
He probably has to say that
for legal reasons.
HOWARD: Uh-oh.
They gave us plain rice
instead of fried rice.
Well, no fair!
I SoulCycled this morning.
I'm entitled to a pile of fat rice.
Well, I would say that this
constitutes a catering crisis.
I agree. Who's gonna
step up and handle it?
Doesn't matter. This is fine.
(INAUDIBLE)
Penny?
What?
You know what?
I'll take care of it.
Done.
You didn't make him
feel bad, did you?
Actually, he was laughing.
I'm really impressed
at how you handled that, Howard.
Please. I've been sending food
back my entire life.
One of my first
full sentences was,
"I had breast milk for breakfast."
Excuse me,
before we start eating,
I would like to make a toast.
- Nice.
If only I could think of one.
Someone else go.
Hey. Here's the sewing kit
you asked for.
Oh, a minute 19.
Quick.
You were timing me?
Yes. I am going through
a bit of a timing phase.
How long will it last?
We'll find out.
What did you need the kit for?
Oh, er...
Sheldon was squatting down
to pick up a fork
and he ripped his pants.
Someone's gonna be sore tomorrow.
(DOOR SHUTS)
Quick thinking.
But for future lies,
this is as far as I can squat.
Penny gets 20 points
for the sewing kit.
Yeah, minus five,
because this is mine.
Well, she's still pulling
a commanding lead.
Did Bernadette even try
to send us a sewing kit?
She did.
Amazon, standard shipping,
not even Prime.
We could've done that ourselves.
(SCOFFS) That's what she said.
Maybe we're being old-fashioned,
defining these roles by gender.
You know, historically,
the best man's role
was to defend the bride
and groom in combat.
I mean, if that's not Penny,
I don't know what we're doing here.
I see your point.
Okay, we are officially open
to a best woman
and a gentleman of honor.
Oh! Those names are terrible.
One point off for you.
What am I being tested for?
Oh, it's not important.
But if you don't pass,
none of this matters.
Okay, what's the next test?
Loyalty.
We need to choose
someone who has our backs,
someone who will keep our
secrets even from each other.
Well, I don't have any secrets
from you.
Do you have secrets from me?
Yes.
Oh, that has been weighing
on me for years.
Come here.
Would you call yourself
a loyal and trustworthy friend?
- Yeah, I like to think so.
- Great.
Because I need to tell you
something about Howard,
but you can't tell him
that I told you.
Nope. Don't want to hear it.
Do not like to engage in gossip.
Okay. I respect your integrity.
Is it about his special underwear?
Because I already know.
And that's all I'll say.
Fine, it has a charcoal filter in it.
It's really sweet of you
to come by and keep me company.
Agreed.
So listen, I have a secret
that I need to tell someone.
But you can never say a word.
Not even to Howard.
I'm your girl. Lay it on me.
Really?
You keep things from your husband?
No, I tell him everything.
Don't be a child.
Okay. Here it is.
I can control the thermostat
in Leonard's apartment with my phone.
And when he makes me mad,
I turn it up, slightly.
Oh. Hey. I didn't know you were here.
What are you two talking about?
Literally, nothing interesting.
Oh, you're good.
Okay, getting to
the ceremony on time.
Leonard, quick.
I need you to get me
to Arcadia within the hour.
The train store's having a sale.
Why can't Amy drive you?
Because of the tradition
that I cannot see Amy
on the day of the train store sale.
Please, please see a doctor.
- Next test.
- Just wait one second.
Is it getting hot in here?
(CHUCKLING)
I'm sorry. Where were we?
How well do our friends know us?
So I was talking to my favorite aunt-
Aunt Doe, right?
Exactly.
Did she ever figure out what
that thing on her knee was?
Turns out it was a chocolate chip.
Mmm, makes sense, she does like to bake.
AMY: Yes, she does. Damn,
you are a thoroughbred.
You know, dealing with cold feet
is an important part of being
both best man and maid of honor.
Maybe we should test for that ability.
You really think
you might get cold feet?
Actually, I was talking about you.
Amy.
If there's one thing in
this world I'm sure of,
you are right to be worried.
Goodnight.
Howard, I've had my eye
on this limited edition Swamp Thing,
but now that I'm
about to buy it,
I'm having second thoughts.
What do you think?
I don't know, Sheldon,
it's pretty expensive.
Yes, but what if it will
make me happy, you know,
waking up and seeing it every
morning for the rest of my life?
(CHUCKLING)
Really, a walking clump of swamp grass?
Yeah, well, Bernadette's
no prize either!
Hey, what you doing?
Er, Sheldon gave me a brain-teaser.
It's kind of fun.
It's about a group of people at dinner,
and you have to figure out where
they can sit without fighting.
Yeah, is this
the one where Mr. Green
can't sit next to anyone eating meat,
and Uncle Light Blue
won't sit next to any
of the darker colors?
Yeah, did Sheldon send it to you?
Amy did.
I solved it already.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Same way I solved
my jury duty summons,
I threw it away.
No, no, no, no, no.
Aunt Orange can't sit next to the bar
without Ms. Pink saying,
"Jesus thinks you've
had enough whiskey."
Did Sheldon and Amy give
you guys that puzzle, too?
Yeah. ls it just me or
have they been acting strange?
I don't think they're acting.
Yeah, the other clay,
Sheldon made me
take him to the train store.
We didn't go inside.
He just said,
"Nicely done,"
and then we went home.
Yeah, and Amy gave me this plastic ring
and told me to hold on to it.
I got one, too.
- Yeah, same.
- Yeah, me, too.
But Cinnamon ate it.
I'll get it back tomorrow.
I have to say,
this is going pretty well.
It is.
If experimenting on humans
is morally wrong,
then I don't want
to be morally right.
Hey, are you testing us
to see who gets to be in your wedding?
- Yes.
- No.
They're rating us.
And I'm in last?
Don't panic, there's still time.
Look, it's a marathon, not a sprint.
You know what, this is so insulting.
I don't even want to be
your stupid best man.
- Yeah.
- Me neither.
Wait, wait.
Just out of curiosity,
which one of you figured it out?
I did.
Impressive.
Hello, Stuart.
Hey, Sheldon.
Can I interest you in a cappuccino?
When did you start selling those?
Someone left it here,
but it's still warm.
Want to say four bucks?
No, thank you.
Everything okay?
Well, I secretly
experimented on my friends,
and now none of them
want to be my best man.
So, you know,
normal wedding drama.
Sorry.
Probably have to use
my stupid brother.
So get ready for a wedding toast
delivered by his armpit.
Well, if you really don't
want to use your brother,
I'd be your best man.
- Really?
- Yeah, we're friends.
Plus, it'd be nice.
Never really been called
the best before.
Or a man, for that matter.
Okay, well, thank you, Stuart.
That's a very generous offer.
My pleasure.
I understand
the best man usually
receives a present.
That's true.
Can never have
too much Claritin.
You're still working on
Sheldon's dumb brain-teaser?
Oh, my God, Dr. Purple's
a woman! Of course!
Oh, that feels so good.
Hello.
I believe I owe the
three of you an apology.
No argument here.
By experimenting on you,
I realize I've violated your trust
and possibly the Geneva Convention.
Is that it?
No.
So as to not upset
any of you further,
I've asked Stuart
to be my best man,
and he's agreed.
Now, you're all still invited
to the bachelor party.
He's thinking Costco
and the theme is browsing.
You picked Stuart over one of us?
Well, I wanted to choose one of you,
but you all turned against me.
Picking a best man isn't
about keeping score.
But you're all my friends.
I mean, if I didn't collect data,
how could I possibly choose
among the three of you?
Well, that's actually kind of sweet.
Is it?
Then perhaps I said it wrong.
Look, this is your wedding,
just pick whoever you want.
You don't need to worry
about anyone else but yourself.
You've kind of been training
for this your whole life.
Thank you, Leonard.
And if it helps,
these two are quitters.
Hey, what you making?
Er. Well, I spilled the cheese packet,
-so we're having mac and nothing.
-(LEONARD SIGHS)
Yeah. I'll just have the mac.
"Nothing" gives me gas.
Why are you in such a good mood?
I just talked to Sheldon.
He apologized about the tests
and asked me to be his best man.
Great. After all you've done
for him, he should've asked you.
And Amy's your best friend.
I'm sure she'll come
to her senses and pick you.
Okay, she's not my best friend.
We're not 12.
If she wants Bernadette
to be her maid of honor,
I really don't care.
Sounds like you care.
No, I mean, it's just annoying.
You know, we talk every day.
We see each other all the time.
She's always there
for me, and basically...
Oh, my God,
Amy's my best friend.
You Okay?
No, my best friend didn't ask me
to be her maid of honor.
I'm pissed!
So, bottom line,
what you did was wrong and cruel,
which the mother of my children
finds oddly appealing.
So she still wants
to be my maid of honor?
Maid of honor, hit woman,
whatever you need.
Make the call.
Look, I know this is your wedding,
and you can do whatever you want,
but if you think anyone but me
is gonna be your maid of honor,
then you're an idiot because
you are my best friend.
- Too late. Bernadette...
- Bestie!
Stuart, I'm sorry if it's weird
Sheldon made me best man
instead of you.
It's okay.
I was best man for two whole days.
No one can take that away from me.
Except for Sheldon, when he did.
Although, if you want to be
a part of the wedding party,
I suppose you could be the flower girl.
Sold.
Well, I thought Halley
was gonna be the flower girl.
Oh. That's much better.
Sorry, Stuart, you're out.
Hey, so is Bernadette okay
with me being maid of honor?
Actually, I haven't
had the courage to tell her.
- I guess I should do that.
- Yeah.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Although, as maid of honor,
your job is to make my life easier.
(SIGHS)
Damn it.
Hey, Stuart, you still
want in on this wedding?
Not that much.
(SIGHS) Fine, I'll do it.
But do me a favor and unlock
the liquor cabinet first.
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
English - SDH